<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recipes on Live for Today</title>
    <link>/recipes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recipes on Live for Today</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
<<<<<<< HEAD
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
=======
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 12:46:50 -0600</lastBuildDate>
>>>>>>> e2ae766308cde03cbdd6f340869c1c952b395778
    
	<atom:link href="/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
<<<<<<< HEAD
      <title>Pan Seared Scallops</title>
      <link>/recipes/seafood_scallops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/seafood_scallops/</guid>
      <description>Heat olive oil in a large skillet over medium-high heat. Add scallops and season the tops with black pepper. Cook 2 minutes, until golden brown. Flip with spatula and cook 2 more minutes, until second side is golden brown.
Add soy sauce mixture to pan and bring to a simmer, for 2 minutes, until sauce thickens and scallops are cooked through and have an opaque color.
Simple and delicious! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ShaoMai</title>
      <link>/recipes/chinese_shaomai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/chinese_shaomai/</guid>
      <description>Shumai or Shaomai or 烧卖 is a type of traditional Chinese dumpling.
Dumpling wraps from a Chinese grocery store.
Ground pork, ginger, chicken broth, soy sauce, chives, and shrimps.
Steam for 18 to 20 mins.
                  </description>
=======
      <title>Daikon Radish Pickle</title>
      <link>/recipes/chinese_diakonpickle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 12:46:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/chinese_diakonpickle/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to make super easy and quick pickled daikon radishes! These pickles are so versatile that they can go with anything!
Directions
 In a mixing bowl, toss sliced diakon with lot of salt. Cover until water is released for 2 days. Drain and rinse daikon, removing as much salt as possible.  Pickle Brine:
 White vinegar 200g Sake 100g Brown sugar 160g Light soy saurce 40g Boil above liquid Pour into pickled can Add Jananese plams Chill for overnight                </description>
>>>>>>> e2ae766308cde03cbdd6f340869c1c952b395778
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baked Spring Roll</title>
      <link>/recipes/chinese_springroll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 12:34:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/chinese_springroll/</guid>
      <description>Delicious and crunchy without deep frying!
Ingredients
 Cabbage Carrot Brown mushroom Spring roll wrapper (7 inch square) Spring roll sauce  Directions
 Shreded cabbage and carrot Stir fry them in sesame oil, don&amp;rsquo;t over cook. Add salt Stir fry sliced mushrooms with oyster sauce until soft
 Preheat oven to 425F
 Arrange spring rolls in a single layer on a medium baking sheet.
 Brush with vegetable oil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
<<<<<<< HEAD
      <title>Daikon Radish Pickle</title>
      <link>/recipes/chinese_diakonpickle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/chinese_diakonpickle/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to make super easy and quick pickled daikon radishes! These pickles are so versatile that they can go with anything! Directions
 In a mixing bowl, toss sliced diakon with lot of salt. Cover until water is released for 2 days. Drain and rinse daikon, removing as much salt as possible.  Pickle Brine:
 White vinegar 200g Sake 100g Brown sugar 160g Light soy saurce 40g Boil above liquid Pour into pickled can Add Jananese plams Chill for overnight                    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
=======
>>>>>>> e2ae766308cde03cbdd6f340869c1c952b395778
      <title>Drink_Coffee</title>
      <link>/recipes/drink_coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/drink_coffee/</guid>
      <description>Cold Brew Coffee is made by brewing roughly ground coffee beans in cold water for a long period of time (think 24 hours). Hot Coffee is brewed by pouring hot water over finely ground coffee in a very short period of time. Iced Coffee is simply Hot Coffee poured over ice.  Cold Brwe Coffee
Instructions: * Roughly ground some fresh coffee beans * Combine the coarsely-ground coffee ans cold water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drinks</title>
      <link>/recipes/drink_cocktail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/drink_cocktail/</guid>
      <description>Pomegranate mojito
Happy Christmas Eve!! I can’t believe today is the last post in the year 2019. Today I am going to finish with a nice, celebratory festive cocktail.
This pomegranate mojito is an easy twist on a classic that tastes more complex than it is. With a delicious tartness, bright color and being so easy to make, it is perfect for any occasion.
Ingredients
 10 mint leaves 1 tbsp sugar 1&amp;frasl;2 lime 1 1&amp;frasl;2 oz white rum 45 ml 3 oz pomegranate juice 90 ml 2 oz sparkling water 60 ml  Instructions * Cut the lime half into 4 wedges * Place the lime wedges, mint leaves and sugar in the bottome of a glass and muddle them together * Top up the glass with ice then pour over the rum * Add the pomegranate juice then topu up the glass with sparkling water * Stir gently to mix</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
<<<<<<< HEAD
=======
      <title>Pan Seared Scallops</title>
      <link>/recipes/seafood_scallops/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 09:44:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/seafood_scallops/</guid>
      <description>Heat olive oil in a large skillet over medium-high heat. Add scallops and season the tops with black pepper. Cook 2 minutes, until golden brown. Flip with spatula and cook 2 more minutes, until second side is golden brown.
Add soy sauce mixture to pan and bring to a simmer, for 2 minutes, until sauce thickens and scallops are cooked through and have an opaque color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
>>>>>>> e2ae766308cde03cbdd6f340869c1c952b395778
      <title>Dry Pot Cauliflower</title>
      <link>/recipes/vegie_cauliflower/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 09:33:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/vegie_cauliflower/</guid>
      <description>Dry Pot Cauliflower is a restaurant favorite that we’ve had countless times in China. It’s our vegetable of choice when eating out. You might think it sounds boring, but we discovered that cauliflower can be amazingly delicious with a little spice, saltiness and the addition of pork belly.
There is a reason why this dish is called Dry Pot Cauliflower, or 干锅菜花 (gan guo cai hua). Restaurants usually serve dishes like this in a miniature wok over a tiny chafing dish flame.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheese Platter</title>
      <link>/recipes/cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/cheese/</guid>
      <description>Cheese is a dairy product derived from milk that is produced in a wide range of flavors, textures, and forms by coagulation of the milk protein casein. It comprises proteins and fat from milk, usually the milk of cows, buffalo, goats, or sheep.
要说火腿界的“扛把子”，非伊比利亚火腿（jamón ibérico)莫属，严格的猪种选择和饲养过程，造就了这种最适合生吃的顶级火腿。 https://zhuanlan.zhihu.com/p/31802634
从2014年4月开始，西班牙国家标准局根据猪的品种纯度、食谱中的橡子比例、饲养方式等因素，规定了伊比利亚火腿的名称和等级。正版的伊比利亚火腿，都由伊比利亚猪的后腿制成，统称为Jamon，分为四个等级（见下图）。而前腿制成的则被称为Paleta。相比较Paleta，Jamon熟成时间长，脂肪含量高，肉质更加柔嫩丰腴。
想有比较好的体验。至少选择橡子增肥的伊比利亚黑猪火腿（Jamón Ibérico de Bellota
要想不糟践伊比利亚火腿，唯一的选择就是生吃，伊比利亚火腿作为开胃菜再好不过了。
几乎所有的西班牙餐厅或酒吧，都备有生火腿，供食客现切现吃，但是赛拉诺还是伊比利亚火腿，是bellota还是cebo，点单的时候就要看清楚了
在马德里，有几家叫做“火腿博物馆”的馆子。虽然名为博物馆，但其实是个售卖火腿、奶酪、小吃和其他餐点的连锁店，店里分为餐厅和bar，花一欧多就可以品尝到夹着一两片火腿的三明治，丰俭由 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salted Duck</title>
      <link>/recipes/meat_saltedduck/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/meat_saltedduck/</guid>
      <description>Salted Duck
Nanjing Salted Duck has over 2000 years of history. It looks plain, but is packed with flavor. You’ll need:
one whole 4 – 4 ½ pound duck 4 tablespoons salt (1/3 cup) 2 ½ tablespoons Sichuan peppercorns (half 1/3 cup) 4 star anise 3 bay leaves 1 cinnamon stick 5 slices ginger 3 scallions, cut into large segments 1/2 cup Shaoxing wine  Directions:
Rinse the duck thoroughly under cold water, discarding any of the giblets that came with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seafood_Paella</title>
      <link>/recipes/seafood_paella/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/seafood_paella/</guid>
      <description>Seafood Paella
This is the dramatic seafood paella that looks stunning. You can vary the quantities of seafood and also use crab, or lobster (boil them separately).
Andresito, who is collecting reminiscences of people in villages around him in Alicante, told me that on the Alicante Coast, fishermen&amp;rsquo;s families made seafood paellas without any vegetables. When they did not go out to fish, they made arroz de piedras with mollusks from the rocks (piedras means rocks).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seafood_Tilapia</title>
      <link>/recipes/seafood_tilapia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/seafood_tilapia/</guid>
      <description>Marinate for fish:
1 tbsp of Chinese cooking wine ½ tsp salt ½ tsp pepper 1 egg white 2 tbsp corn flour
Tilapia with Green Mustard Soup
              Porridge with Tilapia Fillet
Here is another recipe. It is a great breakfast. The Chinese name is 生菜鱼片粥 and English name is fish filet congee.
粥用电饭锅煮好后移到煮菜锅里，加一点色拉油和姜末，烧开后加鱼片煮至鱼片完全变白，再加入生菜丝烫熟。 吃时加盐，葱花，白胡椒粉调味。
Sichuan Water Cooked Fish</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broiled Lobster Tail</title>
      <link>/recipes/seafood_lobster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 15:52:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/seafood_lobster/</guid>
      <description>Broiled Lobster Tail This guide has all you need to know about cooking lobster tails - how to prepare lobster tails (butterfly them), how to cook lobster tails, and the BEST broiled lobster tail recipe - all in just 20 minutes!
Welcome to the ultimate guide to cooking lobster tails! With the flavorful butter sauce and ultra quick cooking method, it’s the best lobster tail recipe for holidays, celebrations, and date nights at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appertizer_ChickenLettuceWrap</title>
      <link>/recipes/appertizer_chickenlettucewrap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 15:44:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/appertizer_chickenlettucewrap/</guid>
      <description>Chicken Lettuce Wrap
Chicken Lettuce Wrap 2018-04-27 No Comments
2018/06/16 Andy’s friend and her son visited us since her son is studying master degree in a Chicago University and this friend came from Canada. We invited them for a dinner at our house.
I want to make a dish not only tasty also nice presentation. I browsed some websites online and found this recipe is simple with nice presentation.
2018/04/27</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Couscous or Quina</title>
      <link>/recipes/appertizer_couscous/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 15:41:49 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/appertizer_couscous/</guid>
      <description>One cup of couscous contains 36 grams of carbohydrates, 2.2 grams of fiber, 6 grams of protein, 0.3 grams of fat, and 176 calories. As such, it is lower in fat and calories than quinoa, but also lower in protein, iron, and magnesium. Couscous is used in many ways that rice would be used, especially as a pilaf
Couscous
Couscous is composed of semolina wheat flour. It&amp;rsquo;s the national dish of Morocco and has been a staple in North Africa for centuries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seafood_Salmon</title>
      <link>/recipes/seafood_salmon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 14:57:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/seafood_salmon/</guid>
      <description>Salmon Flake Lettuce Wrap 2018-07-07 No Comments
Simple ingredient is not only tasty but looking good.
You just need Marinated Salmon from Costco, (little chopped celery is optional) and butterhead lettuce from a grocery store.
Defrost frozen salmon at room temperature. Microwave to cook the salmon for few minutes. Make salmon flakes by using fork and chopsticks when they are still hot or warm and remove the skin. Put flakes on the lettuce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dessert_AppleRose</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_applerose/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 13:58:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_applerose/</guid>
      <description>Apple Rose 2018-10-20 No Comments
Not only look good but taste delicious!
&amp;ldquo;These were inspired by a cook named Ana, a Brazilian food blogger living in Italy. I really hope you give these gorgeous looking, and very delicious apple roses a try soon. Enjoy!&amp;rdquo;
Chef&amp;rsquo;s Notes: If you don&amp;rsquo;t have a microwave, just sauté your apple slices in a little bit of butter over medium heat for about half a minute per side, or until flexible but not soft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese_BeefTendon</title>
      <link>/recipes/chinese_beeftendon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 12:03:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/chinese_beeftendon/</guid>
      <description>Stew Beef Tendon 2018-11-18 No Comments
The beef tendons are used as an ingredient in some Asian cuisines. Tendon is tough and fibrous, but becomes soft after a long period of cooking. It contains large amounts of collagen and after boiling or stewing, it is sometimes described as mimicking the mouthfeel of high-fat cuts of beef despite its low fat content.
Cook beef tendon in a pressure cooker for 90 mins with cooking wine, soy sauce, green onion, giner etc</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese_SpringPancake</title>
      <link>/recipes/chinese_springpancake/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 12:02:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/chinese_springpancake/</guid>
      <description>Steamed Spring Pancakes 2018-11-18 No Comments
Flour and salt hot water to make a dough
make thin flat pancake by using rolling pin spread little oil on top of each pancake stack up
Steam on boiled water</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese_MungBeanJellySalad</title>
      <link>/recipes/chinese_mungbeanjellysalad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 12:01:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/chinese_mungbeanjellysalad/</guid>
      <description>Green Bean Salad 2018-11-18 No Comments
Ratio: 1:6 (1 cup of green bean powder and 6 cups of water)
For sauce:
Garlic Dark Vinegar Oyster sauce Sugar Chinese pepper Chicken powder Cilantro Sesame oil ginger hot sauce (with black bean)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fresh Fruit Platter</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_fruits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 11:56:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_fruits/</guid>
      <description>I like to begin the platter with a base of ripe, colorful, sliced melons and pineapple&amp;ndash;for example, cantaloupe, honeydew, Galia, or Cavaillon melons, plus the new &amp;ldquo;golden&amp;rdquo; pineapples. Peel the outside of a whole melon, cut it in half through the stem end, and scoop out the seeds. Place the melon halves cut side down on a board, and slice them straight across into 1&amp;frasl;2-inch-thick slices. Fan each half-melon out slightly and arrange it on the platter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nuts</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_nuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 11:52:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_nuts/</guid>
      <description>Nuts 2018-11-18 No Comments
Honey Walnuts
375F oven, roasted for 10 to 15 mins
Mix honey and walnuts in a bowl, and then spread them on the parchment paper.
Spice Pecans
Salt, Star Anise, peppercorn, ginger, sugar soak pecans overnight boil in water for 2 hours
170F oven to roast until dry</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dessert_RiceCake</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_ricecake/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 11:51:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_ricecake/</guid>
      <description>Sweet Rice Cake 2018-11-18 No Comments
1 bag of sweet rice flour
1&amp;frasl;2 cup of sugar
3 eggs
1 1&amp;frasl;4 cups of milk or more
1 ts baking powder
1&amp;frasl;3 cup vegetable oil
walnuts / pecan
red bean paste
Add sweet rice flour, sugar, baking powder in a bowl and mix well
Add eggs, milk, and oil in another bowl and mix well (electric mixer)
Add flour into the second bowl to make batter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meat_Chicken</title>
      <link>/recipes/meat_chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 11:49:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/meat_chicken/</guid>
      <description>Sichuan Chicken in Chili Oil Sauce
2018-11-18 No Comments
Cooked one whole chicken, and then cut into small pieces
ginger, green onion, garlic
soy sauce, salt
red flake pepper, peppercorn to blend
peanuts, sesame seeds and cilantro for decoration
Spread hot vegetable oil on the top
Grilled Chicken Tenderlion 2018-09-18 No Comments
Another simple but delicious recipe.
Marinate chicken tenderloin or thigh with your favorite seasoning for couple of hours or overnight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vegie_WoodEarSalad</title>
      <link>/recipes/vegie_woodearsalad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 10:02:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/vegie_woodearsalad/</guid>
      <description>The Woks of Life
Wood Ear Mushroom Salad 凉拌木耳
Well, you don’t see this dish everyday! It’s weird-looking and not particularly appealing at first glance, but this wood ear mushroom salad dish is literally on every menu in China.
I wouldn’t have dared to share this Wood Ear Mushroom Salad recipe a few years back, as very few people outside of Asia know what this ingredient is. But now that we’ve included wood ears in many of our popular recipes from the past few years–like Moo Shu Pork, Moo Shu Chicken, and Chicken with Garlic Sauce–we’re going whole hog on you all with this delicious wood ear appetizer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vegie_Eggplant</title>
      <link>/recipes/vegie_eggplant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:50:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/vegie_eggplant/</guid>
      <description>China Sichuan Food
Roasted Eggplants with Garlic (蒜香烤茄子)
For those who are on a vegan diet, eggplant is the ideal food as a substitute for meats. When well cooked, eggplant is my first choice over any type of meats. In summer days, young and fresh eggplants are almost everywhere in the market. A simplest way is to make a spicy Sichuan style eggplants salad, make an easy red-braised Chinese eggplants with minced pork or stir-fry with green beans or other vegetables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dessert_RedBeanBread</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_redbeanbread/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:40:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_redbeanbread/</guid>
      <description>Red Bean Bread 2018-12-20 No Comments
puffs, red bean paste, egg yolk, Sesame seed
Bake at 375F for 15 mins
Red Bean Bread, An Asian Bakery Favorite
The holy grail. The originator. The classic. The veteran.
Okay, maybe I’m overstating, but something about the red bean bun inspires respect. It’s the old guard. The faithful standby when you don’t want some weirdo questionable scallion, ham, cheese concoction, or you’re just about fed up with dribbling pineapple crumb topping all over your shirt as you walk down the street.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seafood_Mussels</title>
      <link>/recipes/seafood_mussels/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:36:43 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/seafood_mussels/</guid>
      <description>Steamed Mussels 2018-12-24 No Comments
Beer Steamed Mussels with French Bread
Mussels in White Wine
Mussels in White Wine – Almost every bistro in Provence, France has its own version of mussels in white wine. I bought the fresh lived mussels from Costco and followed the recipe to make my own version mussels in white wine. It is wonderful for a light lunch and excellent with a glass of white wine!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seafood_SeaCucumber</title>
      <link>/recipes/seafood_seacucumber/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:33:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/seafood_seacucumber/</guid>
      <description>Braised Sea Cucumber 2018-12-27 No Comments
This is a high protein food in China.
Braised Sea Cucumber With Fish Maw (焖海参花胶) is a very simple dish that every Chinese family can relate and enjoy. It is not only flavourful but also has high nutritional value. Sea cucumber with its gelatinous texture is a delicacy in Chinese cuisines. It is believed to help to prevent aging. Fish maw and pork tendons, on the other hand are a good source of collagen as they improve blood circulation, complexion and heal wound after an operation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meat_BeefShortRibs</title>
      <link>/recipes/meat_beefshortribs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:21:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/meat_beefshortribs/</guid>
      <description>Beef Short Ribs 2018-12-27 No Comments
Korean style table BBQ at home. Ribeye steak, brown mushroom, sweet onion, chili paste, and miso soup paste. Don’t forget green leaf lettuce to wrap the meat and eat. It is much fresh than restaurant food!
Braised Beef Short Ribs
Only 2 ingredients: sliced short ribs and Korean BBQ Sauce.
Instant Pot</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appertizer_PorkJellyFish</title>
      <link>/recipes/appertizer_porkjellyfish/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 08:54:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/appertizer_porkjellyfish/</guid>
      <description>Pork Jelly Dish 2018-12-28 No Comments
Had this dish at my friend’s house and I like it. So I asked her the recipe and just tried by myself. It turned out pretty good. Just need to add garlic soy sauce before serving. I think I will make this dish for my New Year Eve party.
This is what it looks like that made by my friend. I will use cilantro instead of green onion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appertizer_BakedGarlicMushroom</title>
      <link>/recipes/appertizer_bakedgarlicmushroom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 08:51:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/appertizer_bakedgarlicmushroom/</guid>
      <description>Baked Garlic Mushroom
Garlic Butter Mushrooms are a quick and impressive side dish that are a staple for meals in our house where steak is served. They roast in the oven just like your favorite vegetables would and after a quick toss in some butter they are ready to be served.
This year we served these Garlic Butter Mushrooms with the Perfect Prime Rib, Perfect Potato Latkes and my kid’s favorite dish to help me make, Rainbow Roasted Vegetables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dessert_GreenTeaCake</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_greenteacake/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 15:04:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_greenteacake/</guid>
      <description>Macha Cakes 2019-01-04 No Comments
Japanese style layered cake
12 layers cake
Roughly, 60 grams = 1&amp;frasl;2 cup
1/19/2019 – made this cake again. The batter was too thick so it turned out with layers. Also no enough sugar so the taste wasn’t too good.
Making the cake
4 eggs ( 4 egg white, 3 egg yolk) 1/3 cup of sugar 1 tablespoon matcha powder 1/4 cup milk 1 tablespoon vegetable oil 1/3 cup cake flour 1/4 teaspoon baking powder 1/4 teaspoon cream of tarter Bake for 15 mins at 325F degree  Cake Directions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
<<<<<<< HEAD
=======
      <title>ShaoMai</title>
      <link>/recipes/shaomai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 15:02:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/shaomai/</guid>
      <description>Shaomai 2019-01-13 No Comments
Shumai or Shaomai or 烧卖 is a type of traditional Chinese dumpling. Dumpling wraps from a Chinese grocery store. Ground pork, ginger, chicken broth, soy sauce, chives, and shrimps. Steam for 18 to 20 mins
Shaomai 2019-01-13 No Comments
Shumai or Shaomai or 烧卖 is a type of traditional Chinese dumpling. Dumpling wraps from a Chinese grocery store. Ground pork, ginger, chicken broth, soy sauce, chives, and shrimps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
>>>>>>> e2ae766308cde03cbdd6f340869c1c952b395778
      <title>Dessert_SesameCookie</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_sesamecookie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 15:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_sesamecookie/</guid>
      <description>Sesame Cookie 2019-01-13 No Comments
A friend brought this cookie for my party. It tastes pretty good so I will give it a try later.
These delicious sesame seed cookies are coated with toasted sesame seeds. The recipe includes how to toast the sesame seeds. You might also find toasted sesame seeds in bulk.
The cookies are easy to prepare and bake, and they make an excellent snack for any occasion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken</title>
      <link>/recipes/chicken_fajitas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 14:44:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/chicken_fajitas/</guid>
      <description>Skillet Chicken Fajitas
2019-01-30 No Comments
Let’s discuss: Rather than sautéing the ingredients, you simply place the chicken and vegetables into the skillet, toss them with taco seasoning and put the whole pan in the oven to roast. As it’s cooking away, you can prep the tortillas and all of your favorite fixings, like guacamole and salsa. When you remove the sizzling skillet from the oven, it’s dinnertime.
Ingredients for 4 servings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dessert_AppleStrudle</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_applestruddle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 11:29:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_applestruddle/</guid>
      <description>Apple Strudle 2019-02-13 No Comments
Apple Strudle is a German style dessert. It is made with fresh tart apples and cinnamon powder. So deleicious. Apple Strudle is a German style dessert. It is made with fresh tart apples and cinnamon powder. So deleicious.
Apple Strudle is a German style dessert. It is made with fresh tart apples and cinnamon powder. So deleicious. Apple Strudle is a German style dessert. It is made with fresh tart apples and cinnamon powder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vegie_LotusRoot</title>
      <link>/recipes/vegie_lotusroot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 10:58:47 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/vegie_lotusroot/</guid>
      <description>Sweet Lotus Root 2019-03-05 No Comments
A delicious Chinese dish that needs to slow cook for 12 hours and soak in the sauce for another 12 hours to make it sweet and soft. Lotus root has high fiber and other benefits.
Lotus Root 2018-12-27 No Comments
Lotus root is one of my favorite vegetables.
原料：莲藕1节（约250克） 红椒半个 小青椒2个 大葱1节 姜1小块 大蒜1瓣
调料：醋1汤匙 白糖2茶匙（10克） 盐1/4茶匙（1克） 味精1/4茶匙（1克） 花椒15颗 油4汤匙（60ml）
做法：
1）将莲藕削去外皮，切成薄片泡在清水中。大葱，姜，蒜都切成细丝。红椒切丝，小青椒切片。
2）锅中倒入清水，大火煮开后放入莲藕片焯烫半分钟后捞出，放入冷水中浸泡，待冷却后捞出沥干，摆入盘中。调入醋，白糖，盐，味精，葱姜蒜丝，红椒丝和小青椒片。
3）食用油倒入汤勺中，放入花椒，开小火将油烧热，待花椒变成深荔枝皮色，油有点点冒烟时，把火关掉。将花椒油淋在菜上即可。吃前，记得搅拌均匀。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appertizer_ThreadedBeanCurd</title>
      <link>/recipes/appertizer_threadedbeancurd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 10:42:17 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/appertizer_threadedbeancurd/</guid>
      <description>Threaded Bean Curd Salad 2019-04-20 No Comments
Miss Chinese food once a while. So made this new recipe. I learned this appertizer from Din Tai Feng restaurant. The key ingrediant is saseme oil. Miss Chinese food once a while. So made this new recipe. I learned this appertizer from Din Tai Feng restaurant. The key ingrediant is saseme oil. Miss Chinese food once a while. So made this new recipe. I learned this appertizer from Din Tai Feng restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dessert_GelatinDessert</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_gelatindessert/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 10:35:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_gelatindessert/</guid>
      <description>Gelatin Dessert
It is easy to make and presentation also looks great. It is easy to make and presentation also looks great. It is easy to make and presentation also looks great. It is easy to make and presentation also looks great. It is easy to make and presentation also looks great. It is easy to make and presentation also looks great. It is easy to make and presentation also looks great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japanese_Food</title>
      <link>/recipes/japanese_food/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 10:29:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/japanese_food/</guid>
      <description>Japanese Food Series
Will make a dish like this picture!
7/6/2019
Clam Soup Lived clams, kelp, miso paste, sake, basil/green onion/cilantro
5/28/2019
Bought Sashimi from the Japanese supermarket again.
5/18/2019
Sesame noodle for breakfast. Actually this is Chinese version but eat like Japanese:)
5/14/2019
Stopped by at a Japanese supermarket on my way home yesterday. They sale the most fresh sashimi so I made sashimi dinner for two! I bought tuna and yellowtail sashimi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grilling Time at Backyard</title>
      <link>/recipes/grill/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 09:27:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/grill/</guid>
      <description>Grilled Kebab 2019-06-17 No Comments
BBQ season begins this year. I found the new recipes for salmon and steak. I also added more vegetables on kebabs so we can eat not only meat but veggies. The longest time is making skewers. I also prefer to use real steel sticks instead of bamboo sticks. Charcoal is really better than gas grill! The flavor is different!
Steak kebab  Salmon kebab
lamb kebab</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noodle</title>
      <link>/recipes/noodle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 09:25:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/noodle/</guid>
      <description>Hand Made Noodle 2019-07-07 No Comments
8/4/2019 Sunday
Recently, I like this hand pulled noodle very much. I know noodle has lot of carbs that I shouldn’t eat too much. But this noodle is really a delicious Chinese food and it is a great summer dish.
First, you need to make a dough with all purpose flour, 1% salt, and water.
Then, cut them into smaller pieces and cover them with vegetable oil for about 3 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dessert_MoonCake</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_mooncake/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 08:46:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_mooncake/</guid>
      <description>Moon Cake 2019-08-18 No Comments
I think the Chinese mid-autumn festival is around the corner but not sure which day. The moon cake is a dessert cake. I made the moon cake a few times. It is delicious but it takes a lot of time from preparation to finish. I don’t have a plan to make it yet.
My friend made this cake with mung bean and red bean. Edit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dessert_CheeseCake</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_cheesecake/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 08:44:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_cheesecake/</guid>
      <description>Mini Cheesecake 2019-08-26 No Comments
Ingredients For the Crust:
1 1/2 cups graham cracker crumbsfrom 12 whole crackers* 6 Tbsp unsalted butter, melted 1/2 tsp cinnamon  For the Mini Cheesecakes:
16 oz cream cheese from two 8oz packages, softened 3 large eggs room temperature 14 oz sweetened condensed milk  Topping Ingredients:
1 cup caramel sauce 1 cup heavy whipping cream chilled 1 Tbsp granulated sugar 1/2 tsp vanilla extract 1/4 tsp cinnamon to garnish optional  **Cooks Tip: Mixing the condensed milk on LOW speed helps knock out excess air bubbles which can cause the cheesecakes to crack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appertizer - Salsa</title>
      <link>/recipes/appertizer_salsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 20:57:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/appertizer_salsa/</guid>
      <description>Salsa is the Spanish word for &amp;ldquo;sauce&amp;rdquo;. In English, especially in the United States, when the word &amp;ldquo;salsa&amp;rdquo; is used in an unqualified manner, it refers to the spicy tomato-and-chili-based preparation known as salsa roja, salsa picante or salsa cruda, as adopted from Mexican cuisine.
Homemade salsa is not only delicious, it’s very quick and easy to make! I never buy it from a grocery store.
It tastes incredibly fresh which tangy tomatoes, onions and hints of lime, cilantro and cumin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appertizer - Guacamole</title>
      <link>/recipes/appertizer_guacamole/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 20:50:13 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/appertizer_guacamole/</guid>
      <description>Guacamole is an avocado-based dip, spread, or salad first developed by the Aztecs in present-day Mexico. In addition to its use in modern Mexican cuisine, it has become part of international and American cuisine as a dip, condiment and salad ingredient.
It is easy to make, naturally gluten-free and vegan, and always the hit of a party.
Note: Avocados must be riped.
Of course, there are a million ways to use put this guacamole recipe to delicious use as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seafood - Shrimp</title>
      <link>/recipes/seafood_shrimp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 20:40:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/seafood_shrimp/</guid>
      <description>Presentation is more important than eating for me!
I bought the jumbo size white tiger frozen shrimps from Costco, then just simply grill them on Weber grill and assemble them in a plate.
              Marinate defrost shrimps with salt, pepper, and olive oil before pan-fry them. My friend made the shrimp ball soup which is also very delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Layer Cake</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_twolayercake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 19:33:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_twolayercake/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:
 10 eggs
2 x half cup of sugar
2 tablespoon of vegetable oil
1&amp;frasl;2 cup of milk
1 cup of Swans cake flour
1&amp;frasl;2 teaspoon of cream of tarter
1&amp;frasl;2 teaspoon baking powder
Parchment paper
Cooking racks
Icing knife
 Frosting:
 3 cups of heavy cream
1&amp;frasl;4 cup confectioners sugar
1&amp;frasl;2 teaspoon vanilla
Beat cream until it begins to thicken; add sugar gradually, add vanilla,
Until cream holds its shape when the beater is raised</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All About Salad</title>
      <link>/recipes/salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 13:48:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/salad/</guid>
      <description>Napa Cabbage Salad
Sweet pepper, green onion, lettuce, reddish, daikon, and cucumber Salt, white vinegar, sugar, and water Found this recipe in a New York supermarket. This is a Chinese recipe. People like it during the hot summer days. Despite only containing a handful of ingredients, it offers so much in texture, flavor, and contrast. It is elegant and refined, yet simple, approachable, and effortless.
The sweetness of the oranges, the earthy beets, the creamy, satiating avocado chunks, and crunch of toasted hazelnuts come together to create one impressive beet salad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All About Salad</title>
      <link>/recipes/salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 13:48:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/salad/</guid>
      <description>Napa Cabbage Salad
Sweet pepper, green onion, lettuce, reddish, daikon, and cucumber Salt, white vinegar, sugar, and water Found this recipe in a New York supermarket. This is a Chinese recipe. People like it during the hot summer days. Despite only containing a handful of ingredients, it offers so much in texture, flavor, and contrast. It is elegant and refined, yet simple, approachable, and effortless.
The sweetness of the oranges, the earthy beets, the creamy, satiating avocado chunks, and crunch of toasted hazelnuts come together to create one impressive beet salad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soup_Homemade</title>
      <link>/recipes/soup_homemade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 14:06:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/soup_homemade/</guid>
      <description>I always like soup so I always like to make soup by myself. Because in this way, I will know what ingredients are in my soup. I try to not use high fat items in soup, such as cream, butter etc. My soup is always light with less salt too.
Fish Maw Soup Made this soup with canned sweet corn, fish maw, and egg white.
Fish maw is a good source of collagen, which is vital in healthy skin beauty in all age group of either gender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drink_Homemade</title>
      <link>/recipes/drink_homemade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 13:52:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/drink_homemade/</guid>
      <description>Simple homemade drink without sugar. Can add honey if you have a sweet tooth.
This time I added some turmeric powder. Turmeric, sometimes called Indian saffron or the golden spice.
Positive side effects
While turmeric is a spice, it has also traditionally been used in Chinese medicine to treat inflammatory conditions, skin diseases, wounds, digestive,and liver conditions.
Anti-inflammatory properties
The Arthritis Foundation cites several studies in which turmeric has reduced inflammation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Porridge</title>
      <link>/recipes/porridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 13:48:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/porridge/</guid>
      <description>Congee is a type of rice porridge that is popular in many Asian countries, especially East Asia. When eaten as plain rice congee, it is most often served with side dishes.
Pumpkin porridge
Sweet potato porridge
Taro and purple rice porridge
Green bean, red bean, and black bean porridge. Good for hot and humid summer to get rid of wetness from your body. Pressure cook for 2 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rice_with_sausage</title>
      <link>/recipes/rice_with_sausage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 13:42:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/rice_with_sausage/</guid>
      <description>Rice is important for asian. Just like bread is import for Europen. However, they both have carbs and not really good for diet because they will convert to suger in your body and it may cause diabete problem. So now there are a lot of North American people are skipping carbs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Hot Pot</title>
      <link>/recipes/chinese_hot_pot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 21:54:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/chinese_hot_pot/</guid>
      <description>Hot Pot is a Chinese traditional food. It is usually eat in winter. It is best for a group of friends together. 12/4/2019
                                                        10/6/2019</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>