<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recipes on Live for Today</title>
    <link>/recipes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recipes on Live for Today</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 20:57:40 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Appertizer - Salsa</title>
      <link>/recipes/appertizer_salsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 20:57:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/appertizer_salsa/</guid>
      <description>Salsa is the Spanish word for &amp;ldquo;sauce&amp;rdquo;. In English, especially in the United States, when the word &amp;ldquo;salsa&amp;rdquo; is used in an unqualified manner, it refers to the spicy tomato-and-chili-based preparation known as salsa roja, salsa picante or salsa cruda, as adopted from Mexican cuisine.
Homemade salsa is not only delicious, it’s very quick and easy to make! I never buy it from a grocery store.
It tastes incredibly fresh which tangy tomatoes, onions and hints of lime, cilantro and cumin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appertizer - Guacamole</title>
      <link>/recipes/appertizer_guacamole/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 20:50:13 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/appertizer_guacamole/</guid>
      <description>Guacamole is an avocado-based dip, spread, or salad first developed by the Aztecs in present-day Mexico. In addition to its use in modern Mexican cuisine, it has become part of international and American cuisine as a dip, condiment and salad ingredient.
It is easy to make, naturally gluten-free and vegan, and always the hit of a party.
Note: Avocados must be riped.
Of course, there are a million ways to use put this guacamole recipe to delicious use as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seafood - Shrimp</title>
      <link>/recipes/seafood_shrimp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 20:40:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/seafood_shrimp/</guid>
      <description>Presentation is more important than eating for me!
I bought the jumbo size white tiger frozen shrimps from Costco, then just simply grill them on Weber grill and assemble them in a plate.
              Marinate defrost shrimps with salt, pepper, and olive oil before pan-fry them. My friend made the shrimp ball soup which is also very delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Layer Cake</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_twolayercake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 19:33:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_twolayercake/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:
10 eggs 2 x half cup of sugar 2 tablespoon of vegetable oil 1&amp;frasl;2 cup of milk 1 cup of Swans cake flour 1&amp;frasl;2 teaspoon of cream of tarter 1&amp;frasl;2 teaspoon baking powder Wax paper Cooking racks Icing knife
Frosting:
3 cups of heavy cream 1&amp;frasl;4 cup confectioners sugar 1&amp;frasl;2 teaspoon vanilla Beat cream until it begins to thicken; add sugar gradually, add vanilla, Until cream holds its shape when the beater is raised</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
<<<<<<< HEAD
      <title>All About Salad</title>
      <link>/recipes/salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 13:48:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/salad/</guid>
      <description>Napa Cabbage Salad
Sweet pepper, green onion, lettuce, reddish, daikon, and cucumber Salt, white vinegar, sugar, and water Found this recipe in a New York supermarket. This is a Chinese recipe. People like it during the hot summer days. Despite only containing a handful of ingredients, it offers so much in texture, flavor, and contrast. It is elegant and refined, yet simple, approachable, and effortless.
The sweetness of the oranges, the earthy beets, the creamy, satiating avocado chunks, and crunch of toasted hazelnuts come together to create one impressive beet salad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
=======
>>>>>>> cad36587fe9197b7eea9514362c3dec411964e8e
      <title>Soup_Homemade</title>
      <link>/recipes/soup_homemade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 14:06:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/soup_homemade/</guid>
      <description>I always like soup so I always like to make soup by myself. Because in this way, I will know what ingredients are in my soup. I try to not use high fat items in soup, such as cream, butter etc. My soup is always light with less salt too.
Fish Maw Soup Made this soup with canned sweet corn, fish maw, and egg white.
Fish maw is a good source of collagen, which is vital in healthy skin beauty in all age group of either gender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drink_Homemade</title>
      <link>/recipes/drink_homemade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 13:52:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/drink_homemade/</guid>
      <description>Simple homemade drink without sugar. Can add honey if you have a sweet tooth.
This time I added some turmeric powder. Turmeric, sometimes called Indian saffron or the golden spice.
Positive side effects
While turmeric is a spice, it has also traditionally been used in Chinese medicine to treat inflammatory conditions, skin diseases, wounds, digestive,and liver conditions.
Anti-inflammatory properties
The Arthritis Foundation cites several studies in which turmeric has reduced inflammation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Porridge</title>
      <link>/recipes/porridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 13:48:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/porridge/</guid>
      <description>Congee is a type of rice porridge that is popular in many Asian countries, especially East Asia. When eaten as plain rice congee, it is most often served with side dishes.
Pumpkin porridge
Sweet potato porridge
Taro and purple rice porridge
Green bean, red bean, and black bean porridge. Good for hot and humid summer to get rid of wetness from your body. Pressure cook for 2 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rice_with_sausage</title>
      <link>/recipes/rice_with_sausage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 13:42:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/rice_with_sausage/</guid>
      <description>Rice is important for asian. Just like bread is import for Europen. However, they both have carbs and not really good for diet because they will convert to suger in your body and it may cause diabete problem. So now there are a lot of North American people are skipping carbs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Hot Pot</title>
      <link>/recipes/chinese_hot_pot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 21:54:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/chinese_hot_pot/</guid>
      <description>Hot Pot is a Chinese traditional food. It is usually eat in winter. It is best for a group of friends together. 12/4/2019
                                                   10/6/2019</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>