<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Live for Today</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Live for Today</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 12:47:46 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cathy</title>
      <link>/cathy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 12:47:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cathy/</guid>
      <description>MY LIFE, MY TRAVEL
I will finish my travel blog before I go to next trip in this year. In this way, I can digest what I see and what I think during each trip. I want each of my trips to be memorable. It is just for myself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Topolobampo Mexican Restaurant, Chicago IL</title>
      <link>/restaurant/topolobampo_mexican/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:08:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/topolobampo_mexican/</guid>
      <description>Topolobampo Mexican Restaurant 2018-01-27 No Comments
This is a one star Michelin restaurant in Chicago. Went there with my work colleagues for lunch. We had 3-course pre-fixed menu lunch.
The color, presentation, and taste of each dish is so good. This is probably a best Mexican food I ever had!
This is a one star Michelin restaurant in Chicago. Went there with my work colleagues for lunch. We had 3-course pre-fixed menu lunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheese</title>
      <link>/recipes/cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:02:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/cheese/</guid>
      <description>Cheese is a dairy product derived from milk that is produced in a wide range of flavors, textures, and forms by coagulation of the milk protein casein. It comprises proteins and fat from milk, usually the milk of cows, buffalo, goats, or sheep.
Cheese 2018-03-23 No Comments I like this cheese now @ 1/18/2019. It is made in WI.
Cheese becomes my favorite food so I’d like to try all kinds of cheese.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Road Trip from Los Angeles to San Deigo</title>
      <link>/travel/us_ca_sandiego/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 08:49:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_ca_sandiego/</guid>
      <description>A Road Trip from Los Angeles to San Deigo
2018-05-09 1 Comment
Driving along the coast and stunning views – A road trip from Los Angeles to San Diego, CA!
It was Friday afternoon. I was checking the flight to Seattle. Flight status looked good for standbys but I wasn’t sure if it would be a good time to visit Mt Rainier National Park. The park is at high elevation so the temperature will be colder than sea level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US_NM_SantaFe</title>
      <link>/travel/us_nm_santafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 16:03:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_nm_santafe/</guid>
      <description>Protected: Iceland &amp;gt;&amp;gt; New Mexico 2018-05-20 No Comments
5/25/2018 Friday ORD – ABQ
5/26/2018 Saturday Pistachio Tour in NM White Sands National Monument
5/27/2018 Sunday Taos Peublo Village
5/28/2018 Monday Santa Fe, NM Kash-Katuwe Tent Rocks National Monument
5/29/2018 Tuesday ABQ – LAX LAX – ORD
5/29/2018 Tuesday Flying Home
Time to flying home after my adventure. Since I skipped visiting the Carlsbad Caverns National Park, I decided to go home one day earlier as my planned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US_CA_PointReyes</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_ca_pointreyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 15:57:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_ca_pointreyes/</guid>
      <description>Point Reyes National Seashore (2018/04/21) 2018-04-22 No Comments
TRAVEL BEYOND THE ORDINARY!
Had scenic drive along California 1 Highway last weekend and continue to explore California 1 Hwy this weekend. This weekend, the weather is very pleasant about 60 to 70 degrees and clear sunny. So I decided to do a day hiking instead of scenic drive.
After doing little homework, I decided Alamere Falls for hiking. Have seen many waterfalls but this is a tidefall which is rare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broiled Lobster Tail</title>
      <link>/recipes/seafood_lobster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 15:52:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/seafood_lobster/</guid>
      <description>Broiled Lobster Tail This guide has all you need to know about cooking lobster tails - how to prepare lobster tails (butterfly them), how to cook lobster tails, and the BEST broiled lobster tail recipe - all in just 20 minutes!
Welcome to the ultimate guide to cooking lobster tails! With the flavorful butter sauce and ultra quick cooking method, it’s the best lobster tail recipe for holidays, celebrations, and date nights at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appertizer_ChickenLettuceWrap</title>
      <link>/recipes/appertizer_chickenlettucewrap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 15:44:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/appertizer_chickenlettucewrap/</guid>
      <description>Chicken Lettuce Wrap
Chicken Lettuce Wrap 2018-04-27 No Comments
2018/06/16 Andy’s friend and her son visited us since her son is studying master degree in a Chicago University and this friend came from Canada. We invited them for a dinner at our house.
I want to make a dish not only tasty also nice presentation. I browsed some websites online and found this recipe is simple with nice presentation.
2018/04/27</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Couscous or Quina</title>
      <link>/recipes/appertizer_couscous/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 15:41:49 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/appertizer_couscous/</guid>
      <description>One cup of couscous contains 36 grams of carbohydrates, 2.2 grams of fiber, 6 grams of protein, 0.3 grams of fat, and 176 calories. As such, it is lower in fat and calories than quinoa, but also lower in protein, iron, and magnesium. Couscous is used in many ways that rice would be used, especially as a pilaf
Couscous
Couscous is composed of semolina wheat flour. It&amp;rsquo;s the national dish of Morocco and has been a staple in North Africa for centuries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seafood_Paella</title>
      <link>/recipes/seafood_paella/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 15:38:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/seafood_paella/</guid>
      <description>Seafood Paella
This is the dramatic seafood paella that looks stunning, with crustaceans and shellfish. You can vary the quantities of seafood and also use crab, crayfish, or lobster (boil them separately). Andresito, who is collecting reminiscences of people in villages around him in Alicante, told me that on the Alicante Coast, fishermen&amp;rsquo;s families made seafood paellas without any vegetables. When they did not go out to fish, they made arroz de piedras with mollusks from the rocks (piedras means rocks).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Hours in Memphis, TN</title>
      <link>/travel/us_tn_memphis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 15:09:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_tn_memphis/</guid>
      <description>Protected: 20 Hours in Memphis, TN 2018-06-17 1 Comment
Group of four to Memphis, Tennessee. This sounds unusual to me. The flight to MEM was wide open so Dan and his girlfriend also want to visit Memphis. All of us had never been to Memphis yet. So we decided to explore the city together.
Before we made the decision to go together, I sent them my itinerary to checkif they can follow my schedule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seafood_Salmon</title>
      <link>/recipes/seafood_salmon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 14:57:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/seafood_salmon/</guid>
      <description>Salmon Flake Lettuce Wrap 2018-07-07 No Comments
Simple ingredient is not only tasty but looking good.
You just need Marinated Salmon from Costco, (little chopped celery is optional) and butterhead lettuce from a grocery store.
Defrost frozen salmon at room temperature. Microwave to cook the salmon for few minutes. Make salmon flakes by using fork and chopsticks when they are still hot or warm and remove the skin. Put flakes on the lettuce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>McKays Fish &amp; Chip Shop, Pitlochry, Scotland</title>
      <link>/restaurant/mckaysfishandchip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 14:43:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/mckaysfishandchip/</guid>
      <description>McKays Fish &amp;amp; Chip Shop, Pitlochry, Scotland
Address: 142 Atholl Rd, Pitlochry PH16 5AG, UK
The fresh North Sea haddock is very popular.
This property is located on the historical General Wade’s Road constructed during the Jacobite rebellions of the 18th century. It was built as part of King George I’s attempt to repress the Highlands, General Wade constructed a new military road ‘for wheel carriages’ between Dunkeld and Inverness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maxies Bistro, Edinburgh UK</title>
      <link>/restaurant/maxiesbistro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 14:34:37 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/maxiesbistro/</guid>
      <description>Haggis is Scottish traditional food.
Address: 5b Johnston Ter, Edinburgh EH1 2PW United Kingdom
Grassmarket, Old Town
Excellent with outdoor seating. Great food, Great view!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theodore Roosevelt National Park, North Dakota US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_nd_theodoreroosevelt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 14:25:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_nd_theodoreroosevelt/</guid>
      <description>Theodore Roosevelt National Park, North Dakota US
Cannon Ball 2018-08-31 No Comments
It is Labor Day long weekend. I am trying to be out of town. However, many people are traveling during the long weekend. It makes difficult for standby passengers. I had been search so many destinations but they all seemed full flights.
I am going to try Bismark, ND later today. It is a small express flight that has only 50 seats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation201810</title>
      <link>/others/vacation_201809/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 14:19:49 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/vacation_201809/</guid>
      <description>Vacation 2018-09-18 No Comments
Summary:
5 countries in 2 weeks.
 Nuremberg, Germany Munich, Germany Hallstatt, Austria Plitvice Lakes National Park, Croatia Dubronvik, Croatia Split, Croatia Triglav National Park, Slovenia Venice, Italy Dolomites, Italy  01_Germany_Nureberg 02_Austria_Hallstatt 03_Croatia_PlitviceLakesNP 04_Croatia_Dubrovnik 05_Coratia_Split 06Slovenia TriglavNP 07_Italy_Venice 08_Italy_Dolomities 09_Germany_Munich
Munich, Germany (2018&amp;frasl;10) Wirtshaus Zum Straubinger, Munich (2018/10/12) Driving the Dolomites, Italy
Venice, Italy
LIVE THE LIFE! I feel what this mean in Venice. Because of global warming, Venice will be disappears after about 30 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US_WashingtonDC</title>
      <link>/travel/us_washingtondc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 14:10:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_washingtondc/</guid>
      <description>RUNNING WHILE TRAVELING – DC 2018-09-20 1 Comment
RUN WHILE TRAVELING
From now on, I will bring my running shoes with me when I travel. Running is a great workout. It is not only for body but for mind. So I ran when I traveled to DC this time and feeling was great.
Bought one-way ticket to Washington DC today. Didn’t get time to do travel research until last night. DC has many museums and history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Torizen, Schaumburg IL</title>
      <link>/restaurant/torizen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 14:01:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/torizen/</guid>
      <description>Address: 22 E Golf Rd, Schaumburg, IL 60173 Modest strip-mall eatery offering heaping bowls of ramen noodles plus other Japanese dishes.
This place is a real hidden gem. TL&amp;rsquo;s Four Seasons is an excellent Chinese and Japanese restaurant. Their sushi is excellent too.
The staff is very polite and friendly. The food is very high quality, with very generous portions and reasonable prices.
Overall, I recommend this place to everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dessert_AppleRose</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_applerose/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 13:58:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_applerose/</guid>
      <description>Apple Rose 2018-10-20 No Comments
Not only look good but taste delicious!
&amp;ldquo;These were inspired by a cook named Ana, a Brazilian food blogger living in Italy. I really hope you give these gorgeous looking, and very delicious apple roses a try soon. Enjoy!&amp;rdquo;
Chef&amp;rsquo;s Notes: If you don&amp;rsquo;t have a microwave, just sauté your apple slices in a little bit of butter over medium heat for about half a minute per side, or until flexible but not soft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wirtshaus Zum Straubinger, Munich Germany</title>
      <link>/restaurant/wirtshaus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 13:31:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/wirtshaus/</guid>
      <description>Protected: Wirtshaus Zum Straubinger, Munich 2018-10-28 No Comments
Once a great place for Bavarian food!
I was in Munich few times and I had Bavarian dishes before but I am satisfied with this restaurant. The pork is so delicious with big portion. The garden is lovely with falling brown leaves. The servers are very friendly with in their national dress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU_Germany_Munich</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_germany_munich/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 13:29:13 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_germany_munich/</guid>
      <description>Munich, Germany 2018-10-28 No Comments
Munich was my last destination during this vacation. I didn’t have any plans for this city. I decided to just relax and had a walk in the old town. We arrived there at about sunset time but still many people in this area. Many shopping stores were decorated with bright and sparkling lights.
First, we returned the car at the rental place. All rental car companies share the same return location so it is very crowded and you need to wait Hertz people to find you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ginos</title>
      <link>/restaurant/ginos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 12:53:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/ginos/</guid>
      <description>Gino’s, Venice Italy 2018-11-09 No Comments
Address: Rio Terà Lista di Spagna, 157, 30121 Venezia VE, Italy
This was the first restaurant I visited in Italy. The food didn’t disappoint me. The food was authentic and delicious.
Gino&amp;rsquo;s is located not far from the train station. It was the only quiet looking restaurant at the time and that&amp;rsquo;s why I stopped in for a quick bite.
The bruschetta wasn&amp;rsquo;t how I was expecting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU_Italy_Venice</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_italy_venice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 12:36:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_italy_venice/</guid>
      <description>Venice, Italy 2018-11-09 1 Comment
Venice charms, captivates and seduces with its dazzling and unique beauty, encapsulated in its enchanting buildings and picturesque waterways.
Gondola
This was the highlight in Venice, Italy. It is a must to do in Venice. We shared the Gondola with another two people. They were boyfriend and girlfriend relationship. The boy came from Argentina and the girl come from London to meet at Venice.
Gondola service is everywhere in Venice and they only accept cash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US_IN_IndianaDunes</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_in_indianadunes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 12:24:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_in_indianadunes/</guid>
      <description>Indiana Dunes National Lakeshore 2018-08-18 No Comments
Didn’t travel a lot this year since the work kept me crazy busy. Last weekend, I was able to relax in town so our Chinese group went to Indiana Dunes National Lakeshore for a picnic. The weather was about 80F degrees. At the same day, Chicago had Air and Water Show so I thought there weren’t too much people on the beach. As soon as I entered the dunes area, I saw tons of people over there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU_Slovenia_LakeBend</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_slovenia_lakebend/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 12:19:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_slovenia_lakebend/</guid>
      <description>Lake Bled is a lake in the Julian Alps of northwestern Slovenia, where it adjoins the town of Bled. The area is a tourist destination.
The lake lies in a picturesque environment, surrounded by mountains and forests.
Bled Island The island has several buildings, the main one being the pilgrimage church dedicated to the Assumption of Mary, built in its current form near the end of the 17th century, and decorated with remains of Gothic frescos from around 1470 in the presbyterium and rich Baroque equipment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU_Croatia_Split</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_croatia_split/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 12:14:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_croatia_split/</guid>
      <description>Split, Croatia 2018-11-17 No Comments
Cathedral of Saint Domnius
Diocletian’s Palace
Split, Croatia
Split is the second-largest city of Croatia and the largest city of the region of Dalmatia, with about 250,000 people living in its urban area. It lies on the eastern shore of the Adriatic Sea and is spread over a central peninsula and its surroundings.
This route takes you on an adventure through southern Dalmatian from Split to Dubrovnik and features cross-island treks along centuries-old trails on the islands of Brač, Hvar, and Korčula.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU_Slovenia_Ljubljana</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_slovenia_ljubljana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 12:06:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_slovenia_ljubljana/</guid>
      <description>Ljubljana is the capital and largest city of Slovenia. It has been the cultural, educational, economic, political, and administrative center of independent Slovenia since 1991.
Here is a set of shooting about local people.
This city wasn’t in my travel plans. It was on our way to our hotel so we had a quick visit this capital city in a cloudy and rainy afternoon.
This time I decided to shoot some local people instead of myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese_BeefTendon</title>
      <link>/recipes/chinese_beeftendon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 12:03:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/chinese_beeftendon/</guid>
      <description>Stew Beef Tendon 2018-11-18 No Comments
The beef tendons are used as an ingredient in some Asian cuisines. Tendon is tough and fibrous, but becomes soft after a long period of cooking. It contains large amounts of collagen and after boiling or stewing, it is sometimes described as mimicking the mouthfeel of high-fat cuts of beef despite its low fat content.
Cook beef tendon in a pressure cooker for 90 mins with cooking wine, soy sauce, green onion, giner etc</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese_SpringPancake</title>
      <link>/recipes/chinese_springpancake/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 12:02:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/chinese_springpancake/</guid>
      <description>Steamed Spring Pancakes 2018-11-18 No Comments
Flour and salt hot water to make a dough
make thin flat pancake by using rolling pin spread little oil on top of each pancake stack up
Steam on boiled water</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese_MungBeanJellySalad</title>
      <link>/recipes/chinese_mungbeanjellysalad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 12:01:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/chinese_mungbeanjellysalad/</guid>
      <description>Green Bean Salad 2018-11-18 No Comments
Ratio: 1:6 (1 cup of green bean powder and 6 cups of water)
For sauce:
Garlic Dark Vinegar Oyster sauce Sugar Chinese pepper Chicken powder Cilantro Sesame oil ginger hot sauce (with black bean)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fresh Fruit Platter</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_fruits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 11:56:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_fruits/</guid>
      <description>I like to begin the platter with a base of ripe, colorful, sliced melons and pineapple&amp;ndash;for example, cantaloupe, honeydew, Galia, or Cavaillon melons, plus the new &amp;ldquo;golden&amp;rdquo; pineapples. Peel the outside of a whole melon, cut it in half through the stem end, and scoop out the seeds. Place the melon halves cut side down on a board, and slice them straight across into 1&amp;frasl;2-inch-thick slices. Fan each half-melon out slightly and arrange it on the platter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nuts</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_nuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 11:52:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_nuts/</guid>
      <description>Nuts 2018-11-18 No Comments
Honey Walnuts
375F oven, roasted for 10 to 15 mins
Mix honey and walnuts in a bowl, and then spread them on the parchment paper.
Spice Pecans
Salt, Star Anise, peppercorn, ginger, sugar soak pecans overnight boil in water for 2 hours
170F oven to roast until dry</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dessert_RiceCake</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_ricecake/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 11:51:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_ricecake/</guid>
      <description>Sweet Rice Cake 2018-11-18 No Comments
1 bag of sweet rice flour
1&amp;frasl;2 cup of sugar
3 eggs
1 1&amp;frasl;4 cups of milk or more
1 ts baking powder
1&amp;frasl;3 cup vegetable oil
walnuts / pecan
red bean paste
Add sweet rice flour, sugar, baking powder in a bowl and mix well
Add eggs, milk, and oil in another bowl and mix well (electric mixer)
Add flour into the second bowl to make batter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meat_Chicken</title>
      <link>/recipes/meat_chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 11:49:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/meat_chicken/</guid>
      <description>Sichuan Chicken in Chili Oil Sauce
2018-11-18 No Comments
Cooked one whole chicken, and then cut into small pieces
ginger, green onion, garlic
soy sauce, salt
red flake pepper, peppercorn to blend
peanuts, sesame seeds and cilantro for decoration
Spread hot vegetable oil on the top
Grilled Chicken Tenderlion 2018-09-18 No Comments
Another simple but delicious recipe.
Marinate chicken tenderloin or thigh with your favorite seasoning for couple of hours or overnight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US_NV_DeathValley</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_nv_deathvalley/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 11:24:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_nv_deathvalley/</guid>
      <description>Death Valley National Park 2018-11-29 No Comments
Death Valley National Park, NV is North America’s lowest point!
I was in this park few years ago but I couldn’t remember which trails I hiked with my girlfriend. The weather was perfect in November. It was about high 60F everyday.
Artists Palette
Golden Canyon Trail &amp;amp; Gower Gulch Loop
Hiked through sandstone canyons, enjoy the view from Manly Beacon, and explored the golden mudstone hills that make this part of Death Valley look so interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US_NV_ValleyOfFireStatePark</title>
      <link>/travel/us_nv_valleyoffirestatepark/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 10:21:31 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_nv_valleyoffirestatepark/</guid>
      <description>Valley of Fire State Park is a public recreation and nature preservation area covering nearly 46,000 acres located 16 miles south of Overton, Nevada. The state park derives its name from red sandstone formations, the Aztec Sandstone, which formed from shifting sand dunes 150 million years ago.
Address: 29450 Valley of Fire Hwy, Overton, NV 89040
Valley of Fire State Park
Valley of Fire is located in the Mojave Desert approximately 58 miles Northeast of the Las Vegas Strip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NewYearEve_2017</title>
      <link>/parties/newyeareve_2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 10:17:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/newyeareve_2017/</guid>
      <description>Happy Christmas Eve!! I can’t believe today is the last post in the advent calendar series. I’ve had SO much fun bringing you guys a new post every day, and today, we’re finishing with a nice, celebratory festive cocktail!
Every year, I look forward to the festive period so much, then it turns up and is crazier and busier than the year and Christmas day arrives before we know it and somehow I wish I’d taken it a bit slower and spent more time just being in this season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drink_Cocktail</title>
      <link>/recipes/drink_cocktail/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 10:13:53 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/drink_cocktail/</guid>
      <description>Happy Christmas Eve!! I can’t believe today is the last post in the advent calendar series. I’ve had SO much fun bringing you guys a new post every day, and today, we’re finishing with a nice, celebratory festive cocktail!
Every year, I look forward to the festive period so much, then it turns up and is crazier and busier than the year and Christmas day arrives before we know it and somehow I wish I’d taken it a bit slower and spent more time just being in this season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NewYearEve_2016</title>
      <link>/parties/newyeareve_2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 10:06:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/newyeareve_2016/</guid>
      <description>New Year Eve Party – 2016/12/31 2018-12-05 No Comments
7 Lucky Foods to Eat on New Year&#39;s Day Black-Eyed Peas, Greens, and Cornbread. Luck factor: Even folks who aren&#39;t from the Southern United States go all in on eating black-eyed peas and leafy greens for good luck on New Year&#39;s Day. ... Pork. Luck factor: Pork for progress! ... Grapes. ... Pomegranates. ... Fish. ... Noodles and Rice. ... Cakes.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vegie_WoodEarSalad</title>
      <link>/recipes/vegie_woodearsalad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 10:02:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/vegie_woodearsalad/</guid>
      <description>The Woks of Life
Wood Ear Mushroom Salad 凉拌木耳
Well, you don’t see this dish everyday! It’s weird-looking and not particularly appealing at first glance, but this wood ear mushroom salad dish is literally on every menu in China.
I wouldn’t have dared to share this Wood Ear Mushroom Salad recipe a few years back, as very few people outside of Asia know what this ingredient is. But now that we’ve included wood ears in many of our popular recipes from the past few years–like Moo Shu Pork, Moo Shu Chicken, and Chicken with Garlic Sauce–we’re going whole hog on you all with this delicious wood ear appetizer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NewYearEve_2013</title>
      <link>/parties/newyeareve_2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:59:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/newyeareve_2013/</guid>
      <description>New Year Eve Party – 2013/12/31 2018-12-05 No Comments
You can&amp;rsquo;t just pop a bottle and call it a night. If you&amp;rsquo;re hosting a New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve party or pregame this year, you need to go all out. Whether you want to go bold, boho, or keep it elegant, we&amp;rsquo;ve got plenty of ideas on this list to make sure yours is a party for the books. Ahead, fifteen New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve party ideas that promise 2020 will begin on a strong note.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NewYearEve_2018</title>
      <link>/parties/newyeareve_2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:55:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/newyeareve_2018/</guid>
      <description>New Year Eve Party – 2018/12/31 2018-12-16 No Comments Fried Wonton &amp;amp; Tofu Salted Duck
To absolutely no one’s surprise, there is A LOT to see and do this New Year’s Eve in Chicago. And while we’ve been toiling away at our desks, we’ve also been daydreaming about all the events, parties, and down-right blowouts we could be going to on the 31st.
The good news? Since we’ve spent so much time thinking about it, we’ve actually been able to compile a pretty solid list of the best celebrations around the city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vegie_Eggplant</title>
      <link>/recipes/vegie_eggplant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:50:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/vegie_eggplant/</guid>
      <description>China Sichuan Food
Roasted Eggplants with Garlic (蒜香烤茄子)
For those who are on a vegan diet, eggplant is the ideal food as a substitute for meats. When well cooked, eggplant is my first choice over any type of meats. In summer days, young and fresh eggplants are almost everywhere in the market. A simplest way is to make a spicy Sichuan style eggplants salad, make an easy red-braised Chinese eggplants with minced pork or stir-fry with green beans or other vegetables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drink_Coffee</title>
      <link>/recipes/drink_coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:46:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/drink_coffee/</guid>
      <description>Espresso Coffee Drinks 2018-12-16 No Comments
Espresso is coffee of Italian origin, brewed by forcing a small amount of nearly boiling water under pressure through finely ground coffee beans. Espresso is generally thicker than coffee brewed by other methods, has a higher concentration of suspended and dissolved solids, and has crema on top.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dessert_RedBeanBread</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_redbeanbread/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:40:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_redbeanbread/</guid>
      <description>Red Bean Bread 2018-12-20 No Comments
puffs, red bean paste, egg yolk, Sesame seed
Bake at 375F for 15 mins
Red Bean Bread, An Asian Bakery Favorite
The holy grail. The originator. The classic. The veteran.
Okay, maybe I’m overstating, but something about the red bean bun inspires respect. It’s the old guard. The faithful standby when you don’t want some weirdo questionable scallion, ham, cheese concoction, or you’re just about fed up with dribbling pineapple crumb topping all over your shirt as you walk down the street.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seafood_Mussels</title>
      <link>/recipes/seafood_mussels/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:36:43 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/seafood_mussels/</guid>
      <description>Steamed Mussels 2018-12-24 No Comments
Beer Steamed Mussels with French Bread
Mussels in White Wine
Mussels in White Wine – Almost every bistro in Provence, France has its own version of mussels in white wine. I bought the fresh lived mussels from Costco and followed the recipe to make my own version mussels in white wine. It is wonderful for a light lunch and excellent with a glass of white wine!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seafood_SeaCucumber</title>
      <link>/recipes/seafood_seacucumber/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:33:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/seafood_seacucumber/</guid>
      <description>Braised Sea Cucumber 2018-12-27 No Comments
This is a high protein food in China.
Braised Sea Cucumber With Fish Maw (焖海参花胶) is a very simple dish that every Chinese family can relate and enjoy. It is not only flavourful but also has high nutritional value. Sea cucumber with its gelatinous texture is a delicacy in Chinese cuisines. It is believed to help to prevent aging. Fish maw and pork tendons, on the other hand are a good source of collagen as they improve blood circulation, complexion and heal wound after an operation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meat_BeefShortRibs</title>
      <link>/recipes/meat_beefshortribs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:21:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/meat_beefshortribs/</guid>
      <description>Beef Short Ribs 2018-12-27 No Comments
Korean style table BBQ at home. Ribeye steak, brown mushroom, sweet onion, chili paste, and miso soup paste. Don’t forget green leaf lettuce to wrap the meat and eat. It is much fresh than restaurant food!
Braised Beef Short Ribs
Only 2 ingredients: sliced short ribs and Korean BBQ Sauce.
Instant Pot</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meat_SaltedDuck</title>
      <link>/recipes/meat_saltedduck/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:19:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/meat_saltedduck/</guid>
      <description>Salted Duck 2018-12-27 No Comments
Nanjing Salted Duck has over 2000 years of history. It looks plain, but is packed with flavor.
You’ll need:
one whole 4 – 4 ½ pound duck 4 tablespoons salt (1/3 cup) 2 ½ tablespoons Sichuan peppercorns (half 1/3 cup) 4 star anise 3 bay leaves 1 cinnamon stick 5 slices ginger 3 scallions, cut into large segments 1/2 cup Shaoxing wine  Directions:
Rinse the duck thoroughly under cold water, discarding any of the giblets that came with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US_FL_Miami</title>
      <link>/travel/us_fl_miami/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:10:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_fl_miami/</guid>
      <description>2018-12-27 No Comments
A day trip to Miami, FL. Left home at 4am in the morning and back home at 10pm in the evening. Was at Miami about 4 hours but it was a surprised and unplanned trip! The flight was already full. I didn’t think I could have a chance! The departure time was at 7:10am and we got assigned seats at 7am. It was really a surprise. The sky was still dark at 7am.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU_Croatia_PlitvicelLakesNP</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_croatia_plitvicellakesnp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:08:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_croatia_plitvicellakesnp/</guid>
      <description>Plitviče Lakes National Park is a 295-sq.-km forest reserve in central Croatia. It&amp;rsquo;s known for a chain of 16 terraced lakes, joined by waterfalls, that extend into a limestone canyon. Walkways and hiking trails wind around and across the water, and an electric boat links the 12 upper and 4 lower lakes. The latter are the site of Veliki Slap, a 78m-high waterfall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US_CA_BigSur</title>
      <link>/travel/us_ca_bigsur/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:05:39 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_ca_bigsur/</guid>
      <description>Protected: Big Sur, CA 2018-12-27 No Comments
Big Sur is a rugged stretch of California’s central coast between Carmel and San Simeon. Bordered to the east by the Santa Lucia Mountains and the west by the Pacific Ocean, it’s traversed by narrow, 2-lane State Route 1, known for winding turns, seaside cliffs and views of the often-misty coastline. The sparsely populated region has numerous state parks for hiking, camping and beachcombing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spice &amp; Rice Kitchen, San Diego CA</title>
      <link>/restaurant/spicericethaikitchen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 08:59:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/spicericethaikitchen/</guid>
      <description>Spice &amp;amp; Rice Kitchen Address: 7734 Girard Ave C, La Jolla, CA 92037
Unpretentious destination for exotic Thai dishes &amp;amp; lunch combos inside or on the fountainside patio.
We are a Thai restaurant that caters to local La Jolla and San Diego residents area. Our food is freshly made and is vegetarian friendly with no MSG added. Takes Reservations, Walk-Ins Welcome, Good For Groups, Good For Kids, Take Out, Delivery, Catering, Waiter Service and Outdoor Seating</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nuremberg is history in close-up - Nuremberg, Germany</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_germany_nuremberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 08:56:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_germany_nuremberg/</guid>
      <description>Nuremberg, Germany 2018-12-27 No Comments
Nuremberg is the second-largest city of the German federal state of Bavaria after its capital Munich, and its 511,628 inhabitants make it the 14th largest city in Germany.
Nuremberg (Nürnberg), Bavaria’s second-largest city and the unofficial capital of Franconia, is an energetic place where the nightlife is intense and the beer is as dark as coffee. As one of Bavaria’s biggest draws it is alive with visitors year-round, but especially during the spectacular Christmas market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appertizer_PorkJellyFish</title>
      <link>/recipes/appertizer_porkjellyfish/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 08:54:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/appertizer_porkjellyfish/</guid>
      <description>Pork Jelly Dish 2018-12-28 No Comments
Had this dish at my friend’s house and I like it. So I asked her the recipe and just tried by myself. It turned out pretty good. Just need to add garlic soy sauce before serving. I think I will make this dish for my New Year Eve party.
This is what it looks like that made by my friend. I will use cilantro instead of green onion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appertizer_BakedGarlicMushroom</title>
      <link>/recipes/appertizer_bakedgarlicmushroom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 08:51:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/appertizer_bakedgarlicmushroom/</guid>
      <description>Baked Garlic Mushroom
Garlic Butter Mushrooms are a quick and impressive side dish that are a staple for meals in our house where steak is served. They roast in the oven just like your favorite vegetables would and after a quick toss in some butter they are ready to be served.
This year we served these Garlic Butter Mushrooms with the Perfect Prime Rib, Perfect Potato Latkes and my kid’s favorite dish to help me make, Rainbow Roasted Vegetables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dessert_GreenTeaCake</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_greenteacake/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 15:04:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_greenteacake/</guid>
      <description>Macha Cakes 2019-01-04 No Comments
Japanese style layered cake
12 layers cake
Roughly, 60 grams = 1&amp;frasl;2 cup
1/19/2019 – made this cake again. The batter was too thick so it turned out with layers. Also no enough sugar so the taste wasn’t too good.
Making the cake
4 eggs ( 4 egg white, 3 egg yolk) 1/3 cup of sugar 1 tablespoon matcha powder 1/4 cup milk 1 tablespoon vegetable oil 1/3 cup cake flour 1/4 teaspoon baking powder 1/4 teaspoon cream of tarter Bake for 15 mins at 325F degree  Cake Directions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ShaoMai</title>
      <link>/recipes/shaomai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 15:02:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/shaomai/</guid>
      <description>Shaomai 2019-01-13 No Comments
Shumai or Shaomai or 烧卖 is a type of traditional Chinese dumpling. Dumpling wraps from a Chinese grocery store. Ground pork, ginger, chicken broth, soy sauce, chives, and shrimps. Steam for 18 to 20 mins
Shaomai 2019-01-13 No Comments
Shumai or Shaomai or 烧卖 is a type of traditional Chinese dumpling. Dumpling wraps from a Chinese grocery store. Ground pork, ginger, chicken broth, soy sauce, chives, and shrimps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dessert_SesameCookie</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_sesamecookie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 15:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_sesamecookie/</guid>
      <description>Sesame Cookie 2019-01-13 No Comments
A friend brought this cookie for my party. It tastes pretty good so I will give it a try later.
These delicious sesame seed cookies are coated with toasted sesame seeds. The recipe includes how to toast the sesame seeds. You might also find toasted sesame seeds in bulk.
The cookies are easy to prepare and bake, and they make an excellent snack for any occasion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morton_Steakhouse</title>
      <link>/restaurant/morton_steakhouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 14:57:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/morton_steakhouse/</guid>
      <description>Morton’s The Steakhouse
Morton&amp;rsquo;s The Steakhouse is a chain of steak restaurants with locations in the United States and franchised abroad, founded in Chicago in 1978. It is a wholly owned subsidiary of Landry&amp;rsquo;s, Inc.
Morton&amp;rsquo;s The Steakhouse at Wacker Place is located at the epicenter of some of Downtown Chicago&amp;rsquo;s most celebrated attractions and downtown hotels. Walking distance from the Magnificent Mile, Millennium Park and the Chicago Theatre District, this steakhouse offers a superb dining location for a business power lunch, after work drinks and small plate $5 Bar Bites, an exceptional dinner or even over 4,000 square feet of private dining space in six private dining rooms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sam &amp; Harry’s Steakhouse</title>
      <link>/restaurant/sam_harry_steakhouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 14:52:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/sam_harry_steakhouse/</guid>
      <description>Sam &amp;amp; Harry’s Steakhouse Sam_Harry_Steakhouse 2019-01-27
Upscale, contemporary steakhouse serving surf &amp;lsquo;n&amp;rsquo; turf classics in the Renaissance Schaumburg Hotel. Address: 1551 Thoreau Dr N, Schaumburg, IL 60173
Sam &amp;amp; Harry&amp;rsquo;s is about savoring the high life. Enjoy innovative cuisine, prime steaks, and fine seafood in an upscale, inviting atmosphere. Our inspired contemporary American menu celebrates thoughtful preparations of the freshest ingredients from local farms, and our Award-Winning wine program includes 250 wines by the bottle and over 50 by the glass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seafood_Tilapia</title>
      <link>/recipes/seafood_tilapia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 14:51:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/seafood_tilapia/</guid>
      <description>Tilapia with Green Mustard Soup
Seasoned Tilapia Fillet 2019-01-30 No Comments Ingredients
2 tilapia fillets (6 ounces each) 1 tablespoon butter, melted 1 teaspoon Montreal steak seasoning 1/2 teaspoon dried parsley flakes 1/4 teaspoon paprika 1/4 teaspoon dried thyme 1/8 teaspoon onion powder 1/8 teaspoon salt 1/8 teaspoon pepper Dash garlic powder  Directions
Preheat oven to 425°. Place tilapia in a greased 11×7-in. baking dish; drizzle with butter. In a small bowl, mix remaining ingredients; sprinkle over fillets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken</title>
      <link>/recipes/chicken_fajitas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 14:44:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/chicken_fajitas/</guid>
      <description>Skillet Chicken Fajitas
2019-01-30 No Comments
Let’s discuss: Rather than sautéing the ingredients, you simply place the chicken and vegetables into the skillet, toss them with taco seasoning and put the whole pan in the oven to roast. As it’s cooking away, you can prep the tortillas and all of your favorite fixings, like guacamole and salsa. When you remove the sizzling skillet from the oven, it’s dinnertime.
Ingredients for 4 servings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US_TX_SanAntonio</title>
      <link>/travel/us_tx_sanantonio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 13:19:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_tx_sanantonio/</guid>
      <description>San Antonio, TX 2019-02-13 No Comments
San Antonio Missions National Historical Park
Visitor Center – Visitor Center at Mission San José
Open seven days a week from 9 am – 5 pm
6701 San Jose Drive, San Antonio, TX 78214
Mission Addresses
Mission Concepción 807 Mission Road, San Antonio, Texas 78210
Mission San José 6701 San Jose Drive, San Antonio, TX 78214
Mission San Juan 9101 Graf Road, San Antonio, Texas 78214</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dessert_AppleStrudle</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_applestruddle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 11:29:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_applestruddle/</guid>
      <description>Apple Strudle 2019-02-13 No Comments
Apple Strudle is a German style dessert. It is made with fresh tart apples and cinnamon powder. So deleicious. Apple Strudle is a German style dessert. It is made with fresh tart apples and cinnamon powder. So deleicious.
Apple Strudle is a German style dessert. It is made with fresh tart apples and cinnamon powder. So deleicious. Apple Strudle is a German style dessert. It is made with fresh tart apples and cinnamon powder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vegie_LotusRoot</title>
      <link>/recipes/vegie_lotusroot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 10:58:47 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/vegie_lotusroot/</guid>
      <description>Sweet Lotus Root 2019-03-05 No Comments
A delicious Chinese dish that needs to slow cook for 12 hours and soak in the sauce for another 12 hours to make it sweet and soft. Lotus root has high fiber and other benefits.
Lotus Root 2018-12-27 No Comments
Lotus root is one of my favorite vegetables.
原料：莲藕1节（约250克） 红椒半个 小青椒2个 大葱1节 姜1小块 大蒜1瓣
调料：醋1汤匙 白糖2茶匙（10克） 盐1/4茶匙（1克） 味精1/4茶匙（1克） 花椒15颗 油4汤匙（60ml）
做法：
1）将莲藕削去外皮，切成薄片泡在清水中。大葱，姜，蒜都切成细丝。红椒切丝，小青椒切片。
2）锅中倒入清水，大火煮开后放入莲藕片焯烫半分钟后捞出，放入冷水中浸泡，待冷却后捞出沥干，摆入盘中。调入醋，白糖，盐，味精，葱姜蒜丝，红椒丝和小青椒片。
3）食用油倒入汤勺中，放入花椒，开小火将油烧热，待花椒变成深荔枝皮色，油有点点冒烟时，把火关掉。将花椒油淋在菜上即可。吃前，记得搅拌均匀。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CookingWithCathy_Dumpling</title>
      <link>/parties/cookingwithcathy_dumpling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 10:55:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/cookingwithcathy_dumpling/</guid>
      <description>Rainbow Dumpling
Protected: Rainbow Dumpling 2019-03-29
I grouped few people together who have same interest about cooking. Rainbow dumpling is our first episode of Cooking with Cathy! They brought dumpling fillings and I prepared doughs. We made wraps and dumplings together. That was fun time with friends.
I got the idea from Pinterest app. We are not only making food but for fun!
4 of us made dumplings Spinach, beets, water Pan fried pot stickers Steamed dumplings We all enjoyed our dumplings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polaris</title>
      <link>/others/polaris/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 10:53:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/polaris/</guid>
      <description>2019-03-29
If I get a Polaris seat, my trip becomes luxury. It means the seat is wider, private, 180 degree flat bed, and good drinks, delicious food.
London Heathrow Airport also has a lounge for you to take a shower after landing. I landed here at 6am in the morning so I took a shower before I headed to London city.
We used to have Global First class cabin that was better than Global business class cabin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lao Sze Chuan</title>
      <link>/restaurant/lao_sze_chuan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 10:49:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/lao_sze_chuan/</guid>
      <description>Lao Sze Chuan Address: 520 N Michigan Ave, Chicago IL
Spicy and salty dishes for me so I am not crazy about this place even though it is a famous restaurant. Spicy and salty dishes for me so I am not crazy about this place even though it is a famous restaurant. Spicy and salty dishes for me so I am not crazy about this place even though it is a famous restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WithKaren</title>
      <link>/others/withkaren/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 10:44:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/withkaren/</guid>
      <description>Karen is one of my best friends in Michigan.
We barely meet after I moved to IL. This summer at April 10th, 2019, she came to Chicago for a Microsoft Conference with her boss and we got a chance to hang out together.
We had a walk in the city and took some pictures during the sunset. Then we went to a Chinese restaurant for dinner. It is a famous restaurant in Michigan Ave, Chicago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appertizer_ThreadedBeanCurd</title>
      <link>/recipes/appertizer_threadedbeancurd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 10:42:17 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/appertizer_threadedbeancurd/</guid>
      <description>Threaded Bean Curd Salad 2019-04-20 No Comments
Miss Chinese food once a while. So made this new recipe. I learned this appertizer from Din Tai Feng restaurant. The key ingrediant is saseme oil. Miss Chinese food once a while. So made this new recipe. I learned this appertizer from Din Tai Feng restaurant. The key ingrediant is saseme oil. Miss Chinese food once a while. So made this new recipe. I learned this appertizer from Din Tai Feng restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CookingWithCathy_Fondue</title>
      <link>/parties/cookingwithcathy_fondue/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 10:38:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/cookingwithcathy_fondue/</guid>
      <description>2019-04-22
Still can’t get together with other friends yet since we all are busy here and there. However our next party will be fondue party. I did some research about food.
4/28/2019 seems another winterstorm day. I was planning out of town but the weather forecast freaked me out. It is better to stay at home to worry free about flights. So I contacted my friends right after work at Friday to gather people together for the Fondue Party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dessert_GelatinDessert</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_gelatindessert/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 10:35:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_gelatindessert/</guid>
      <description>Gelatin Dessert
It is easy to make and presentation also looks great. It is easy to make and presentation also looks great. It is easy to make and presentation also looks great. It is easy to make and presentation also looks great. It is easy to make and presentation also looks great. It is easy to make and presentation also looks great. It is easy to make and presentation also looks great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CookingWithCathy_Noodle</title>
      <link>/parties/cookingwithcathy_noodle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 10:32:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/cookingwithcathy_noodle/</guid>
      <description>Cooking with Cathy – episode 3.
Today is also the last day for Game of Thrones. We are all fan of it so I got together to cook first and then watch the finale together at my basement.
The ending of Game of Thrones made people upset. However, I think that is what it is. No matter what kind of ending is, people will always not satisfied. For me, I think, the story is not ending yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japanese_Food</title>
      <link>/recipes/japanese_food/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 10:29:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/japanese_food/</guid>
      <description>Japanese Food Series 2019-04-29 No Comments
Will make a dish like this picture!
7/6/2019
Clam Soup Lived clams, kelp, miso paste, sake, basil/green onion/cilantro
5/28/2019
Bought Sashimi from the Japanese supermarket again.
5/18/2019
Sesame noodle for breakfast. Actually this is Chinese version but eat like Japanese:)
5/14/2019
Stopped by at a Japanese supermarket on my way home yesterday. They sale the most fresh sashimi so I made sashimi dinner for two!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grilling Time at Backyard</title>
      <link>/recipes/grill/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 09:27:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/grill/</guid>
      <description>Grilled Kebab 2019-06-17 No Comments
BBQ season begins this year. I found the new recipes for salmon and steak. I also added more vegetables on kebabs so we can eat not only meat but veggies. The longest time is making skewers. I also prefer to use real steel sticks instead of bamboo sticks. Charcoal is really better than gas grill! The flavor is different!
Steak kebab  Salmon kebab
lamb kebab</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noodle</title>
      <link>/recipes/noodle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 09:25:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/noodle/</guid>
      <description>Hand Made Noodle 2019-07-07 No Comments
8/4/2019 Sunday
Recently, I like this hand pulled noodle very much. I know noodle has lot of carbs that I shouldn’t eat too much. But this noodle is really a delicious Chinese food and it is a great summer dish.
First, you need to make a dough with all purpose flour, 1% salt, and water.
Then, cut them into smaller pieces and cover them with vegetable oil for about 3 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dessert_MoonCake</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_mooncake/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 08:46:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_mooncake/</guid>
      <description>Moon Cake 2019-08-18 No Comments
I think the Chinese mid-autumn festival is around the corner but not sure which day. The moon cake is a dessert cake. I made the moon cake a few times. It is delicious but it takes a lot of time from preparation to finish. I don’t have a plan to make it yet.
My friend made this cake with mung bean and red bean. Edit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dessert_CheeseCake</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_cheesecake/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 08:44:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_cheesecake/</guid>
      <description>Mini Cheesecake 2019-08-26 No Comments
Ingredients For the Crust:
1 1/2 cups graham cracker crumbsfrom 12 whole crackers* 6 Tbsp unsalted butter, melted 1/2 tsp cinnamon  For the Mini Cheesecakes:
16 oz cream cheese from two 8oz packages, softened 3 large eggs room temperature 14 oz sweetened condensed milk  Topping Ingredients:
1 cup caramel sauce 1 cup heavy whipping cream chilled 1 Tbsp granulated sugar 1/2 tsp vanilla extract 1/4 tsp cinnamon to garnish optional  **Cooks Tip: Mixing the condensed milk on LOW speed helps knock out excess air bubbles which can cause the cheesecakes to crack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THE WORLD AT YOUR FEET - Canadian Rocky Mountains</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/canada_rockymountains/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 08:41:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/canada_rockymountains/</guid>
      <description>THE WORLD AT YOUR FEET
Andy and I like adventures. We like to explore new places. We like to try new food. We like new scenic drives. As a world heritage site, Banff National Park offers rugged beauty, unspoiled landscapes and pristine mountain ranges.
Our first visit was at October 15, 2010. At that time, the summer was over and the fall season began. We had to wear our down coats but the scenery was amazing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cooking with Cathy - Kebab</title>
      <link>/parties/cookingwithcathy_kebab/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 08:30:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/cookingwithcathy_kebab/</guid>
      <description>Cooking with Cathy – episode 4.
Hosted this episode with friends before the summer end. It was a pleasant Saturday afternoon, we made charcoal grilled kebab together.
Actually, I did shopping at Friday and prepared food since Friday evening. I just let them to put chunked lamb on skewers. If I waited them to make food from scratch, it would take hours to finish.
Cooking with Cathy is just for fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet Vincent</title>
      <link>/others/meetvincent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 08:00:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/meetvincent/</guid>
      <description>Recently I am a fan of Vincent. I like his sunflowers painting and Starry Night paint and gracefully I got opportunities to see the real paintings in person.
London, UK has a special exhibition during 3/27/2019 and 08/11/2019 that is about Van Gogh and Britain at Tate Britain Museum.
Vincent’s paintings were not famous when he was alive.
Always continue walking a lot and loving nature, for this’s the real way to learn to understand art better and better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running while Traveling – Dallas, Texas</title>
      <link>/travel/us_tx_dallas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 21:33:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_tx_dallas/</guid>
      <description>A short trip to Dallas, TX. This was my 2nd time to land at DFW airport. A couple of years ago, I was here for a Microsoft Ignite Training where was located in Irving, TX. I did some travel research about Dallas but it seems a little boring city for me because I was looking for some outdoor activities. However, Dallas is a very flat area without mountains. I wasn’t able to find things that I really wanted to explore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tower Bridge - London, United Kingdom</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_uk_london_towerbridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 15:57:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_uk_london_towerbridge/</guid>
      <description>Tower Bridge is a combined bascule and suspension bridge in London, built between 1886 and 1894. The bridge crosses the River Thames close to the Tower of London and has become an iconic symbol of London. Because of this, Tower Bridge is sometimes confused with London Bridge, situated some 0.5 mi (0.80 km) upstream.
Tower Bridge Exhibition can take you to the top of the bridge, equipped with a glass floor, as well as to the bottom to the bridge’s engine rooms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London, United Kingdom</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_uk_london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 15:54:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_uk_london/</guid>
      <description>I knew I should not have a trip during spring break. However, I couldn’t refuse the London opportunity. There were two events that attracted me very much, Van Gogh Exhibition at Tote Britain and European Cups Game at West Ham Stadium.
I am not a soccer fan but I wanted to watch a real game in person in my life time. Glad this was fulfilled now. It is removed from my bucket list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet Fresh Dessert Restaurnat</title>
      <link>/restaurant/meetfresh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 15:32:44 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/meetfresh/</guid>
      <description>Meet Fresh Dessert Restaurnat 鮮芋仙
Meet Fresh is a Taiwanese dessert restaurant chain, with locations in Asia, Australia, New Zealand, Canada and the United States. Corporate headquarters are in New Taipei City. Founded in 2007, the chain specializes in fresh Taiwanese desserts, including soft taro balls and herbed jelly.
Bottom is shaved ice. Authentic Taiwanese exquisite desserts
Sister and Brother Fu grew up in a family which has been farming for generations in the Feng Yuan District of Taichung, Taiwan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Din Tai Fung</title>
      <link>/restaurant/din_tai_fung/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 15:15:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/din_tai_fung/</guid>
      <description>Din Tai Feng Restaurant 鼎泰豐
Din Tai Fung is a Taiwanese restaurant franchise, specialising in Huaiyang cuisine. Outside Taiwan, Din Tai Fung also has branches in Australia, China, Hong Kong, Indonesia, Japan, Macau, Malaysia, Philippines, Singapore, South Korea, United States, Thailand, UK and the UAE. It is a world-renowned Taiwanese restaurant that specializes in soup dumplings and noodles.
Xiao Long Bao is their signature food.
              </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>La La Trip</title>
      <link>/travel/us_ca_antelopevalley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 15:12:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_ca_antelopevalley/</guid>
      <description>The movie of La La Land explores the joy and pain of pursuing their dreams in Los Angeles, CA. I watched this movie last year. It was a great story even though they couldn’t be together at the end but the girl fulfilled her dream in Hollywood.
I haven’t visited La La Land for couple of years so we flew to LAX at midnight of 4/12/2019. It was poppy flower season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden of the Gods, Colorado US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_co_gardenofthegods/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 15:01:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_co_gardenofthegods/</guid>
      <description>Garden of the Gods is on my bucket list for couple of years. My original plan was a weekend trip. However, I made this trip in one day. From Denver airport to the garden was only about one and half hour driving. However, the highway is toll. The round trip cost $35 that was same amount for renting a SUV! That surprised me!
The Colorado landscape looks interesting.
What an adventure!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grand Teton National Park, Wyoming US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_wy_grandteton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 14:50:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_wy_grandteton/</guid>
      <description>Labor Day Weekend Trip
How long haven’t we flied out? Almost two months this summer. Today, we came to the departure lobby in the airport and it looked unfamiliar and we felt we missed it somehow.
This was a busy travel weekend. More and more people took airplanes for traveling. US economy goes very well. We went to economy parking lot G but unfortunately it was full so we had to use our alternative parking lot and then took a cab to the terminal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starry Starry Night</title>
      <link>/others/song_starrynight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 14:31:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/song_starrynight/</guid>
      <description>Starry, starry night
Paint your palette blue and grey
Look out on a summer’s day
With eyes that know the darkness in my soul
Shadows on the hills
Sketch the trees and the daffodils
Catch the breeze and the winter chills
In colors on the snowy linen land
 Vincent Van Gogh – one of the world’s foremost artists. I like few of his colorful and dynamic paints, Starry Starry Night and Sunflowers!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Book</title>
      <link>/others/movie_greenbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 14:24:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/movie_greenbook/</guid>
      <description>Green Book, this is the first movie that I watched since this year. The film is inspired by the true story of a tour of the Deep South by Jamaican-American classical &amp;amp; jazz pianist and Italian-American bounder who served as a driver &amp;amp; bodyguard.
The film won the Oscar Academy Award for Best Picture, as well as Best Original Screenplay and Best Supporting Actor and was also nominated for Best Actor and Best Film Editing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones</title>
      <link>/others/tvshow_gameofthrones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 14:19:42 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/tvshow_gameofthrones/</guid>
      <description>I had been watching GOT all seasons 2 times. However, I still like it very much and now I start watching GOT from season 1 again. This time, I feel I could understand it better than last time. 7 Kingdoms, which one do I like most? The Queen, the dragon mother, Jon Snow? I have to think about it!
4/14/2019
Tonight will have Game of Thrones season 8. This will be the last season of Game of Thrones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadership</title>
      <link>/others/leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 13:46:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/leadership/</guid>
      <description>Year 2018
Year 2017
From around the globe, more than 2,000 leaders came together to celebrate our people, our potential and our passion. Luckily, I had the opportunity to attend this 3-day event. We deepened our understanding of the ecompany’s most important priorities, and continued to build momentum and values and leadership model.
10 ways to have a better conversation
 No multi-task (Put away your phone / Focus on conversation) No lecture participate (Don’t change sb’s mind / Better listener / Everyone you’ll meet, you will learn!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sun-Worshipping Plants</title>
      <link>/others/sunworshippingplants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 13:41:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/sunworshippingplants/</guid>
      <description>Barrington Hills Farm Address: 2790 Spring Creek Road, Barrington Hills, IL 60010
My friend posts some sunflower pictures on WeChat Moments. So I was curious where she went for taking those beautiful sunflower pictures. Surprisingly, it is in Barrington Hills, IL. I was so excited and invited my other friends to go together for photo shooting.
Usually, the best time for taking picture is either morning or sunset time. We went over there at Sunday late afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>365 Miles</title>
      <link>/others/365miles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 12:54:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/365miles/</guid>
      <description>7/12/2019
I wrote down what I ate for couple of weeks and I think they are pretty healthy food with low carb. However I still have fat belly. I am not sure what is wrong with my diet or exercise until yesterday!
In a new WeChat Tomato Group that are people who had reading a book for 14 days, I found out the root cause.
有氧无氧是指糖在运动中是无氧代谢还是有氧代谢。有氧代谢一个葡萄糖能产生38个ATP供细胞使用，过程比较慢。走路就是有氧运动。剧烈运动的时候是无氧代谢，快速产生ATP, 副产品就是乳酸
So it means I should do intense exercise, like short distance and full speed running instead of walking for 30 mins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It is time to take reading to the next level</title>
      <link>/others/bookreading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 11:59:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/bookreading/</guid>
      <description>I usually don&amp;rsquo;t read a book until this year. Now reading becomes a new hobby for me. It is time for me to take my reading to the next level. Now, imagine five years into the future. What might my life look like if I adopted a reading habit, starting today!
 The goal of higher income is not just bigger piles of money. The goal of longer lives is not jsut extra time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CathySummary</title>
      <link>/others/cathysummary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 11:18:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/cathysummary/</guid>
      <description>Year 2020 Planns
 A new song / month Reading Finance investment Travel journey Travel AWS Cert  It is almost end of the year again. Time flies and I need to pause here and recall what have I done during year 2019.
Year 2019
 Starting reading books
 This is becoming a new hobby to me. I met a new friend who introduced me to join a reading club on WeChat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flying Home</title>
      <link>/others/flyinghome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 08:46:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/flyinghome/</guid>
      <description>10/23/2019
We got a room available for my mom in this senior house so we decided to go back to my hometown together.
The trip was smooth even though it was a long international trip from US to Canada to US to China. We had 4 connections. Andy and I didn’t sleep too much during this trip because the schedule was very tight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appertizer - Salsa</title>
      <link>/recipes/appertizer_salsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 20:57:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/appertizer_salsa/</guid>
      <description>Salsa is the Spanish word for &amp;ldquo;sauce&amp;rdquo;. In English, especially in the United States, when the word &amp;ldquo;salsa&amp;rdquo; is used in an unqualified manner, it refers to the spicy tomato-and-chili-based preparation known as salsa roja, salsa picante or salsa cruda, as adopted from Mexican cuisine.
Homemade salsa is not only delicious, it’s very quick and easy to make! I never buy it from a grocery store.
It tastes incredibly fresh which tangy tomatoes, onions and hints of lime, cilantro and cumin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appertizer - Guacamole</title>
      <link>/recipes/appertizer_guacamole/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 20:50:13 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/appertizer_guacamole/</guid>
      <description>Guacamole is an avocado-based dip, spread, or salad first developed by the Aztecs in present-day Mexico. In addition to its use in modern Mexican cuisine, it has become part of international and American cuisine as a dip, condiment and salad ingredient.
It is easy to make, naturally gluten-free and vegan, and always the hit of a party.
Note: Avocados must be riped.
Of course, there are a million ways to use put this guacamole recipe to delicious use as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seafood - Shrimp</title>
      <link>/recipes/seafood_shrimp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 20:40:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/seafood_shrimp/</guid>
      <description>Presentation is more important than eating for me!
I bought the jumbo size white tiger frozen shrimps from Costco, then just simply grill them on Weber grill and assemble them in a plate.
              Marinate defrost shrimps with salt, pepper, and olive oil before pan-fry them. My friend made the shrimp ball soup which is also very delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Layer Cake</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_twolayercake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 19:33:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_twolayercake/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:
10 eggs 2 x half cup of sugar 2 tablespoon of vegetable oil 1&amp;frasl;2 cup of milk 1 cup of Swans cake flour 1&amp;frasl;2 teaspoon of cream of tarter 1&amp;frasl;2 teaspoon baking powder Wax paper Cooking racks Icing knife
Frosting:
3 cups of heavy cream 1&amp;frasl;4 cup confectioners sugar 1&amp;frasl;2 teaspoon vanilla Beat cream until it begins to thicken; add sugar gradually, add vanilla, Until cream holds its shape when the beater is raised</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All About Salad</title>
      <link>/recipes/salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 13:48:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/salad/</guid>
      <description>Napa Cabbage Salad
Sweet pepper, green onion, lettuce, reddish, daikon, and cucumber Salt, white vinegar, sugar, and water Found this recipe in a New York supermarket. This is a Chinese recipe. People like it during the hot summer days. Despite only containing a handful of ingredients, it offers so much in texture, flavor, and contrast. It is elegant and refined, yet simple, approachable, and effortless.
The sweetness of the oranges, the earthy beets, the creamy, satiating avocado chunks, and crunch of toasted hazelnuts come together to create one impressive beet salad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O Canada – Visiting Windsor, Ontario</title>
      <link>/travel/canada_on_windsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 10:26:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/canada_on_windsor/</guid>
      <description>O Canada! Our home and native land!
True patriot love in all of us command.
 Canada was the first foreign country where I went abroad. I dealt with a new language, new way of thinking, new culture, which opened my eyes and changed my perspective of life completely.
Windsor, Ontario Canada is the place actually changed me. I consider it as my second hometown because not only I got my CS degree but my mom is living there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bison – Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_wy_yellowstone_bison/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 10:22:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_wy_yellowstone_bison/</guid>
      <description>The American bison symbolizes the spirit of the west!
 At the same day seven years ago, Andy and I visited the park and first time saw bison in person. We were so excited but with little nervous. People jumped out of their cars to get closer look at a herd of bison. However, there were rangers with us. So we felt much safer! Picture taken at 9/1/2012
Hayden Valley, Yellowstone NP with its broad expense of grasses, has been a home to bison for thousands of years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow in the footsteps of “Game of Thrones” - Dubrovnik, Croatia</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_croatia_dubrovnik/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 10:08:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_croatia_dubrovnik/</guid>
      <description>It’s not easy being drunk all the time. If it were easy, everyone would do it. – Tyrion Lannister
 Game of Thrones is likely one of the most talked about TV shows of the decade and Dubrovnik, Croatia has been a renowned Game of Thrones filming location. After all Dubrovnik is King’s Landing, the capital of the Seven Kingdoms! Dubrovnik’s architecture, City Walls, its open and narrow streets made of big stone blocks helped Dubrovnik to change personality quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A “real life” Postcard – Hallstatt, Austria</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_austria_hallstatt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 09:32:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_austria_hallstatt/</guid>
      <description>Hallstatt is an umber-picturesque town in Austria. Surrounded by the massive Dachstein mountains, this town is a visual treat to the sore eyes. It features on the list of most romantic towns in Europe.
Being a travel geek, I had seen numerous pictures of Hallstatt and had a mental note of visiting this fascinating town someday. This town was on our way to Croatia so we decided to stay there for one night during our European road trip in year 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>God’s Back Garden – the Dolomites, Italy</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_italy_dolomites/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 09:06:52 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_italy_dolomites/</guid>
      <description>God’s Back Garden – the Dolomites, Italy
The Dolomites in the North of Italy boast some of the mightiest granite peaks of Europe. This region is home to a spectacular road that provides both exhilarating and scenic driving.
The breathtaking region around the Dolomites of Italy is one of the most beautiful places on earth. We visited it in October which the fall color was changing that made our road trip more romantic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Square of the Gate of Heavenly Peace - Beijing, China</title>
      <link>/travel/asia_china_beijing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 10:17:52 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/asia_china_beijing/</guid>
      <description>Up there with Times Square in USA, Red Square in Russia, and St. Peter’s Square in Rome, Tiananmen Square in China is among the world’s most famous public spaces. It is the heart of Beijing, China.
                The square is the geographic, political and tourist center of the city, which makes it unavoidable. When I came back from my hometown to Beijing by night train, I made a quick visit at Oct 30, 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation or Duty - China</title>
      <link>/travel/asia_china_shimataigreatwall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 15:37:43 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/asia_china_shimataigreatwall/</guid>
      <description>I gave myself a homework. I need to write a post on my blog after my each trip or adventure. I have came back from China for couple of days but my mind is not calm and I don’t know how to writ down this trip still. It is complicated. This trip mixed with some elements that I hadn’t been experienced yet!
A month ago before my vacation, I borrowed about 20 travel books from the library because I was planning to go to Africa or Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today</title>
      <link>/others/anniversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 15:21:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/anniversary/</guid>
      <description>9/12/2019 Wedding Anniversary Today is mid-autumn festival in China. Today is also my wedding anniversary in US. Today is to remember!
We usually don&amp;rsquo;t celebrate our birthdays. We like to celebrate Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day instead.
Recently, I read a book and it says that treat today is your last day so you won&amp;rsquo;t waste your time! I am to a degree if it is a positive day.
                      6/13/2019 Dating anniversary</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BY THE DEEP BLUE SEA</title>
      <link>/travel/us_ca_la_sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 15:16:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_ca_la_sea/</guid>
      <description>The sea is filled with water, With high and low tides. When we go near it, We feel that we are in paradise! The warmth of the sand touching the feet, The feel of the breeze with a welcoming greet. The sight of the people playing on the shore, Makes my heart roar likes never before! Time flew by as I tried explorer, The beautiful treasures yet the sea bore. Feeling satisfied we flew home, With memories to cherish forever more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall in the Catskills, New York, US</title>
      <link>/travel/us_ny_catskills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 15:09:52 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_ny_catskills/</guid>
      <description>There is no better way to take in the foliage than adventuring outside! This year, Andy and I flew to Albany, NY and then drove about one and half hours to Catskills Mountains in New York State on October 12, 2019. We did the Catskills Mountains Scenic Drive. The roads are winding and surrounded by dense forest with gentle change in elevation. It is a perfect Fall destination. The roads were quiet without too much traffic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Party_Soccer_Team</title>
      <link>/parties/party_soccer_team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 14:40:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/party_soccer_team/</guid>
      <description>This party was finally over and got relief now. Hosting a party for soccer team is stressful than others because they are Andy’s friends. We made food plan together and started to prepare it couple of days earlier in order to make sure the party would be successful.
Bought a box of frozen crab legs from Costco. We decided to serve them a seafood theme dinner.
Appetizers: fried tofu &amp;amp; wonton</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soup_Homemade</title>
      <link>/recipes/soup_homemade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 14:06:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/soup_homemade/</guid>
      <description>I always like soup so I always like to make soup by myself. Because in this way, I will know what ingredients are in my soup. I try to not use high fat items in soup, such as cream, butter etc. My soup is always light with less salt too.
Fish Maw Soup Made this soup with canned sweet corn, fish maw, and egg white.
Fish maw is a good source of collagen, which is vital in healthy skin beauty in all age group of either gender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drink_Homemade</title>
      <link>/recipes/drink_homemade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 13:52:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/drink_homemade/</guid>
      <description>Simple homemade drink without sugar. Can add honey if you have a sweet tooth.
This time I added some turmeric powder. Turmeric, sometimes called Indian saffron or the golden spice.
Positive side effects
While turmeric is a spice, it has also traditionally been used in Chinese medicine to treat inflammatory conditions, skin diseases, wounds, digestive,and liver conditions.
Anti-inflammatory properties
The Arthritis Foundation cites several studies in which turmeric has reduced inflammation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Porridge</title>
      <link>/recipes/porridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 13:48:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/porridge/</guid>
      <description>Congee is a type of rice porridge that is popular in many Asian countries, especially East Asia. When eaten as plain rice congee, it is most often served with side dishes.
Pumpkin porridge
Sweet potato porridge
Taro and purple rice porridge
Green bean, red bean, and black bean porridge. Good for hot and humid summer to get rid of wetness from your body. Pressure cook for 2 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rice_with_sausage</title>
      <link>/recipes/rice_with_sausage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 13:42:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/rice_with_sausage/</guid>
      <description>Rice is important for asian. Just like bread is import for Europen. However, they both have carbs and not really good for diet because they will convert to suger in your body and it may cause diabete problem. So now there are a lot of North American people are skipping carbs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 22:04:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>cathy cathy&amp;hellip;
How to create navigation menus in Hugo https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E6bhmixcR5k
RUN WHILE TRAVELING
Running is good for mind as much as body. Starting a week with a run clears head and leaves happier, more confident, and more positive. Running out is nothing like the drudgery 苦差事 of a treadmill; it’s a way to explore and see places from a new perspective. What has surprised me most is the joy that running can bring me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Hot Pot</title>
      <link>/recipes/chinese_hot_pot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 21:54:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/chinese_hot_pot/</guid>
      <description>Hot Pot is a Chinese traditional food. It is usually eat in winter. It is best for a group of friends together. 12/4/2019
                                                        10/6/2019</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Land of Red Rocks - Sedona, AZ</title>
      <link>/travel/us_az_devilsbridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 21:12:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_az_devilsbridge/</guid>
      <description>We were in Sodona, Arizona - the land of red rocks. Flew to Phoenix, AZ airport and then drove 2 hours to Sedona area for a day trip at November 16, 2019. It was a sunny and beautiful day. The temperature was about 70ish degrees without any wind. Arizona is a great escape destination from the cold weather. The song of 500 Miles Away From Home was a perfect song for this scenic road trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geysers – Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_wy_yellowstone_geysers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 10:16:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_wy_yellowstone_geysers/</guid>
      <description>Something from another planet – Geysers, Yellowstone National Park!
 Andy and I landed at Jackson Hole, Wyoming airport at 6pm 8/30/2019. Was planning for this trip for some time now, we were so excited. We have been visited many national parks but Yellowstone is one of my favorites. The park is located mostly in the Northern Wyoming, adjacent to Montana and Idaho states.
Just before landing the view was picturesque.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gourmet Chinese Food</title>
      <link>/parties/chunhuangcooking_20190810/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/chunhuangcooking_20190810/</guid>
      <description>Gourmet Chinese Food
One of my friends is really good at cooking Chinese food. It is not only delicious but beautiful presentation! They are much better than restaurant food.
She spent lot of time to prepare them from scratch. We always eat more than we could.
This is seafood soup which I like it very much.
The crispy basil is so impressive.
Japanese rice wine from Costco. This tea set cost RMB 5000 because they made with pure gold and silver!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Independence Holiday, Manhattan NY</title>
      <link>/travel/us_ny_manhattan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 15:30:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_ny_manhattan/</guid>
      <description>“We must be free not because we claim freedom, but because we practice it.” – William Faulkner  This year the independence holiday is Thursday so we took Friday off in order to have a long weekend. I spent 3 hours to find a less crowded flight routes at Tuesday night but seems like not possible. All flights were full with negative numbers. Lot of Americans would travel around the world during this summer that made standby was difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tundra – Rocky Mountain NP, Colorado US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_co_rockymountain_tundra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 10:28:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_co_rockymountain_tundra/</guid>
      <description>Rocky Mountain National Park in Colorado, US encompasses mountains, forests, and alpine tundra. Andy and I visited this park a few times before. This time we just wanted to see tundra.
The word tundra means a land without trees. Tundra is a type of biome where the tree growth is hindered by low temperatures and short growing seasons. There are three types of tundra: Arctic tundra, Alpine tundra, and Antarctica tundra.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBQ_Garden</title>
      <link>/restaurant/bbq_garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/bbq_garden/</guid>
      <description>BBQ Garden
My friend invited us to her birthday at BBQ Garden this Saturday 6/22/2019. Met few new friends. Also table grilled BBQ was delicious.
It is buffet style BBQ. You can order as much as you can eat. There are many meat options but my favorite is still beef short ribs.
They also include sushi and Korean style side dishes. I like this restaurant. I would go back!
I made the cake for her and everyone likes my cake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Li Dong&#39;s Birthday Party</title>
      <link>/parties/20190421_lidongbday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 21:08:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/20190421_lidongbday/</guid>
      <description>2019-04-21
It is one of Andy’s best friend’s 50th birthday so I hosted a party with a small group for him at my home. I also make a special birthday cake for him and let his wife to write sth on the cake. I also invited another couple who have similar life style like us.
It is also Eastern Weekend so bought fresh flowers for the holiday.                               </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Party_Chinese_Crab</title>
      <link>/parties/party_chinese_crab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/party_chinese_crab/</guid>
      <description>Crab Party 2018-10-21 No Comments
I am terrified of nightclubs. I hate loud bars. And I get lost at concerts. This makes Friday and Saturday nights as a non-80 something difficult.
As soon as it was socially age appropriate, I began to shift people from raves and bar crawls into game nights and dinner parties.
My first dinner party was a quasi-disaster. There were a ton of appetizers and dessert, but not enough real food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dip into the regions – Highlands, Scotland</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_scotland_highlands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 14:09:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_scotland_highlands/</guid>
      <description>Dip into the regions – Highlands, Scotland
Scotland is one of the most beautiful natural countries around the world. The Scottish Highlands are the home of mountains, glens, and rivers. It is no wonder why they appear as locations in so many movies or TV shows, like Mel Gibson’s self-directed film “Brave Heart”, James Bond’s Skye Fall in “007” movie, “Harry Potter” etc.
There are quite a few ways to get the Highlands, either by train, bus, or car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BAREFOOT ADVENTURE – Edinburgh, Scotland</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_scotland_edinburgh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 14:31:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_scotland_edinburgh/</guid>
      <description>BAREFOOT ADVENTURE – Edinburgh, Scotland
Scotland is an interesting and exciting place to visit. We took a direct flight from Chicago to EDI (Edinburgh International Airport) for my barefoot adventure in July, 2018.
Edinburgh is Scotland’s capital and is not a big city like London and most of attractions are in the medieval old town area, so they are all walking distance. The most interested place is Edinburgh Castle and Royal Miles for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of miles away from home</title>
      <link>/travel/asia_china_shenyang01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 14:51:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/asia_china_shenyang01/</guid>
      <description>Took a week off even though I was very busy at work. My mom planned to go back to China in April. I had to drop her off at our hometown from Windsor, to Chicago, to Beijing, to Shenyang. It was a long trip and would across three countries, Canada, US, and China.
Andy took the Friday off so he flew to Detroit and rented a SUV from Hertz and then drove to Windsor to pick my mom up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CathyPersonalItems</title>
      <link>/others/cathypersonalitems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/cathypersonalitems/</guid>
      <description>Arthritis Patients Respond Very Well to Curcumin Supplements
Arthritis is a common problem in Western countries. There are several different types, most of which involve inflammation in the joints.
Given that curcumin is a potent anti-inflammatory compound, it makes sense that it may help with arthritis. Several studies show this to be true.
In a study in people with rheumatoid arthritis, curcumin was even more effective than an anti-inflammatory drug.Trusted Source</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Temple of the Sea - Monaco</title>
      <link>/europe/monaco/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/monaco/</guid>
      <description>The Principality of Monaco is about 15km (9.3 miles) from the state border with Italy. The city is a resort for tourists and a tax haven for businesses. It is a small country so you can visit it in few hours because the whole state is not larger than 2 square kilometers which is half size of New York&amp;rsquo;s Central Park. We played by ear in this small charm country at Nov 17, 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>