<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Live for Today</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Live for Today</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 15:57:57 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tower Bridge - London, United Kingdom</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_uk_london_towerbridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 15:57:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_uk_london_towerbridge/</guid>
      <description>Tower Bridge is a combined bascule and suspension bridge in London, built between 1886 and 1894. The bridge crosses the River Thames close to the Tower of London and has become an iconic symbol of London. Because of this, Tower Bridge is sometimes confused with London Bridge, situated some 0.5 mi (0.80 km) upstream.
Tower Bridge Exhibition can take you to the top of the bridge, equipped with a glass floor, as well as to the bottom to the bridge’s engine rooms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London, United Kingdom</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_uk_london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 15:54:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_uk_london/</guid>
      <description>I knew I should not have a trip during spring break. However, I couldn’t refuse the London opportunity. There were two events that attracted me very much, Van Gogh Exhibition at Tote Britain and European Cups Game at West Ham Stadium.
I am not a soccer fan but I wanted to watch a real game in person in my life time. Glad this was fulfilled now. It is removed from my bucket list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet Fresh Dessert Restaurnat</title>
      <link>/restaurant/meetfresh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 15:32:44 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/meetfresh/</guid>
      <description>Meet Fresh Dessert Restaurnat 鮮芋仙
Meet Fresh is a Taiwanese dessert restaurant chain, with locations in Asia, Australia, New Zealand, Canada and the United States. Corporate headquarters are in New Taipei City. Founded in 2007, the chain specializes in fresh Taiwanese desserts, including soft taro balls and herbed jelly.
Bottom is shaved ice. Authentic Taiwanese exquisite desserts
Sister and Brother Fu grew up in a family which has been farming for generations in the Feng Yuan District of Taichung, Taiwan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Din Tai Fung</title>
      <link>/restaurant/din_tai_fung/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 15:15:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/din_tai_fung/</guid>
      <description>Din Tai Feng Restaurant 鼎泰豐
Din Tai Fung is a Taiwanese restaurant franchise, specialising in Huaiyang cuisine. Outside Taiwan, Din Tai Fung also has branches in Australia, China, Hong Kong, Indonesia, Japan, Macau, Malaysia, Philippines, Singapore, South Korea, United States, Thailand, UK and the UAE. It is a world-renowned Taiwanese restaurant that specializes in soup dumplings and noodles.
Xiao Long Bao is their signature food.
              </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>La La Trip</title>
      <link>/travel/us_ca_antelopevalley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 15:12:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_ca_antelopevalley/</guid>
      <description>The movie of La La Land explores the joy and pain of pursuing their dreams in Los Angeles, CA. I watched this movie last year. It was a great story even though they couldn’t be together at the end but the girl fulfilled her dream in Hollywood.
I haven’t visited La La Land for couple of years so we flew to LAX at midnight of 4/12/2019. It was poppy flower season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden of the Gods, Colorado US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_co_gardenofthegods/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 15:01:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_co_gardenofthegods/</guid>
      <description>Garden of the Gods is on my bucket list for couple of years. My original plan was a weekend trip. However, I made this trip in one day. From Denver airport to the garden was only about one and half hour driving. However, the highway is toll. The round trip cost $35 that was same amount for renting a SUV! That surprised me!
The Colorado landscape looks interesting.
What an adventure!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grand Teton National Park, Wyoming US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_wy_grandteton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 14:50:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_wy_grandteton/</guid>
      <description>Labor Day Weekend Trip
How long haven’t we flied out? Almost two months this summer. Today, we came to the departure lobby in the airport and it looked unfamiliar and we felt we missed it somehow.
This was a busy travel weekend. More and more people took airplanes for traveling. US economy goes very well. We went to economy parking lot G but unfortunately it was full so we had to use our alternative parking lot and then took a cab to the terminal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starry Starry Night</title>
      <link>/others/song_starrynight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 14:31:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/song_starrynight/</guid>
      <description>Starry, starry night
Paint your palette blue and grey
Look out on a summer’s day
With eyes that know the darkness in my soul
Shadows on the hills
Sketch the trees and the daffodils
Catch the breeze and the winter chills
In colors on the snowy linen land
 Vincent Van Gogh – one of the world’s foremost artists. I like few of his colorful and dynamic paints, Starry Starry Night and Sunflowers!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Book</title>
      <link>/others/movie_greenbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 14:24:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/movie_greenbook/</guid>
      <description>Green Book, this is the first movie that I watched since this year. The film is inspired by the true story of a tour of the Deep South by Jamaican-American classical &amp;amp; jazz pianist and Italian-American bounder who served as a driver &amp;amp; bodyguard.
The film won the Oscar Academy Award for Best Picture, as well as Best Original Screenplay and Best Supporting Actor and was also nominated for Best Actor and Best Film Editing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones</title>
      <link>/others/tvshow_gameofthrones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 14:19:42 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/tvshow_gameofthrones/</guid>
      <description>I had been watching GOT all seasons 2 times. However, I still like it very much and now I start watching GOT from season 1 again. This time, I feel I could understand it better than last time. 7 Kingdoms, which one do I like most? The Queen, the dragon mother, Jon Snow? I have to think about it!
4/14/2019
Tonight will have Game of Thrones season 8. This will be the last season of Game of Thrones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadership</title>
      <link>/others/leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 13:46:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/leadership/</guid>
      <description>Year 2018
Year 2017
From around the globe, more than 2,000 leaders came together to celebrate our people, our potential and our passion. Luckily, I had the opportunity to attend this 3-day event. We deepened our understanding of the ecompany’s most important priorities, and continued to build momentum and values and leadership model.
10 ways to have a better conversation
 No multi-task (Put away your phone / Focus on conversation) No lecture participate (Don’t change sb’s mind / Better listener / Everyone you’ll meet, you will learn!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sun-Worshipping Plants</title>
      <link>/others/sunworshippingplants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 13:41:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/sunworshippingplants/</guid>
      <description>Barrington Hills Farm Address: 2790 Spring Creek Road, Barrington Hills, IL 60010
My friend posts some sunflower pictures on WeChat Moments. So I was curious where she went for taking those beautiful sunflower pictures. Surprisingly, it is in Barrington Hills, IL. I was so excited and invited my other friends to go together for photo shooting.
Usually, the best time for taking picture is either morning or sunset time. We went over there at Sunday late afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>365 Miles</title>
      <link>/others/365miles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 12:54:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/365miles/</guid>
      <description>7/12/2019
I wrote down what I ate for couple of weeks and I think they are pretty healthy food with low carb. However I still have fat belly. I am not sure what is wrong with my diet or exercise until yesterday!
In a new WeChat Tomato Group that are people who had reading a book for 14 days, I found out the root cause.
有氧无氧是指糖在运动中是无氧代谢还是有氧代谢。有氧代谢一个葡萄糖能产生38个ATP供细胞使用，过程比较慢。走路就是有氧运动。剧烈运动的时候是无氧代谢，快速产生ATP, 副产品就是乳酸
So it means I should do intense exercise, like short distance and full speed running instead of walking for 30 mins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Club</title>
      <link>/others/bookreading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 11:59:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/bookreading/</guid>
      <description>I usually don&amp;rsquo;t read a book until this year. Now reading becomes a new hobby for me.
 The goal of higher income is not just bigger piles of money. The goal of longer lives is not jsut extra time. The ultimate goal is to have the freedom to do what we want.
from book of Factufulness
 Reading Activity  The Thorn Birds Novel (online) Day Trading for Dummies, 4th Edition (Safari Bookshelf) Managing the Unmanageable Rules, Tools, and Insights for Managing Software Poeple and Teams Never Split the Difference Becoming by Michelle Obama Meditation &amp;amp; Mindfulness                Read Books in Year 2019  Never Split the Difference (2019&amp;frasl;08)  This book was recommanded by WeChat Reading Club and they also shared the book URL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CathySummary</title>
      <link>/others/cathysummary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 11:18:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/cathysummary/</guid>
      <description>Year 2020 Planns
 A new song / month Reading Finance investment Travel journey Travel AWS Cert  It is almost end of the year again. Time flies and I need to pause here and recall what have I done during year 2019.
Year 2019
 Starting reading books
 This is becoming a new hobby to me. I met a new friend who introduced me to join a reading club on WeChat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flying Home</title>
      <link>/others/flyinghome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 08:46:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/flyinghome/</guid>
      <description>10/23/2019
We got a room available for my mom in this senior house so we decided to go back to my hometown together.
The trip was smooth even though it was a long international trip from US to Canada to US to China. We had 4 connections. Andy and I didn’t sleep too much during this trip because the schedule was very tight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appertizer - Salsa</title>
      <link>/recipes/appertizer_salsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 20:57:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/appertizer_salsa/</guid>
      <description>Salsa is the Spanish word for &amp;ldquo;sauce&amp;rdquo;. In English, especially in the United States, when the word &amp;ldquo;salsa&amp;rdquo; is used in an unqualified manner, it refers to the spicy tomato-and-chili-based preparation known as salsa roja, salsa picante or salsa cruda, as adopted from Mexican cuisine.
Homemade salsa is not only delicious, it’s very quick and easy to make! I never buy it from a grocery store.
It tastes incredibly fresh which tangy tomatoes, onions and hints of lime, cilantro and cumin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appertizer - Guacamole</title>
      <link>/recipes/appertizer_guacamole/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 20:50:13 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/appertizer_guacamole/</guid>
      <description>Guacamole is an avocado-based dip, spread, or salad first developed by the Aztecs in present-day Mexico. In addition to its use in modern Mexican cuisine, it has become part of international and American cuisine as a dip, condiment and salad ingredient.
It is easy to make, naturally gluten-free and vegan, and always the hit of a party.
Note: Avocados must be riped.
Of course, there are a million ways to use put this guacamole recipe to delicious use as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seafood - Shrimp</title>
      <link>/recipes/seafood_shrimp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 20:40:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/seafood_shrimp/</guid>
      <description>Presentation is more important than eating for me!
I bought the jumbo size white tiger frozen shrimps from Costco, then just simply grill them on Weber grill and assemble them in a plate.
              Marinate defrost shrimps with salt, pepper, and olive oil before pan-fry them. My friend made the shrimp ball soup which is also very delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Layer Cake</title>
      <link>/recipes/dessert_twolayercake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 19:33:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/dessert_twolayercake/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:
10 eggs 2 x half cup of sugar 2 tablespoon of vegetable oil 1&amp;frasl;2 cup of milk 1 cup of Swans cake flour 1&amp;frasl;2 teaspoon of cream of tarter 1&amp;frasl;2 teaspoon baking powder Wax paper Cooking racks Icing knife
Frosting:
3 cups of heavy cream 1&amp;frasl;4 cup confectioners sugar 1&amp;frasl;2 teaspoon vanilla Beat cream until it begins to thicken; add sugar gradually, add vanilla, Until cream holds its shape when the beater is raised</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All About Salad</title>
      <link>/recipes/salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 13:48:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/salad/</guid>
      <description>Napa Cabbage Salad
Sweet pepper, green onion, lettuce, reddish, daikon, and cucumber Salt, white vinegar, sugar, and water Found this recipe in a New York supermarket. This is a Chinese recipe. People like it during the hot summer days. Despite only containing a handful of ingredients, it offers so much in texture, flavor, and contrast. It is elegant and refined, yet simple, approachable, and effortless.
The sweetness of the oranges, the earthy beets, the creamy, satiating avocado chunks, and crunch of toasted hazelnuts come together to create one impressive beet salad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O Canada – Visiting Windsor, Ontario</title>
      <link>/travel/canada_on_windsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 10:26:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/canada_on_windsor/</guid>
      <description>O Canada! Our home and native land!
True patriot love in all of us command.
 Canada was the first foreign country where I went abroad. I dealt with a new language, new way of thinking, new culture, which opened my eyes and changed my perspective of life completely.
Windsor, Ontario Canada is the place actually changed me. I consider it as my second hometown because not only I got my CS degree but my mom is living there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bison – Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_wy_yellowstone_bison/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 10:22:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_wy_yellowstone_bison/</guid>
      <description>The American bison symbolizes the spirit of the west!
 At the same day seven years ago, Andy and I visited the park and first time saw bison in person. We were so excited but with little nervous. People jumped out of their cars to get closer look at a herd of bison. However, there were rangers with us. So we felt much safer! Picture taken at 9/1/2012
Hayden Valley, Yellowstone NP with its broad expense of grasses, has been a home to bison for thousands of years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow in the footsteps of “Game of Thrones” - Dubrovnik, Croatia</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_croatia_dubrovnik/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 10:08:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_croatia_dubrovnik/</guid>
      <description>It’s not easy being drunk all the time. If it were easy, everyone would do it. – Tyrion Lannister
 Game of Thrones is likely one of the most talked about TV shows of the decade and Dubrovnik, Croatia has been a renowned Game of Thrones filming location. After all Dubrovnik is King’s Landing, the capital of the Seven Kingdoms! Dubrovnik’s architecture, City Walls, its open and narrow streets made of big stone blocks helped Dubrovnik to change personality quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A “real life” Postcard – Hallstatt, Austria</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_austria_hallstatt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 09:32:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_austria_hallstatt/</guid>
      <description>Hallstatt is an umber-picturesque town in Austria. Surrounded by the massive Dachstein mountains, this town is a visual treat to the sore eyes. It features on the list of most romantic towns in Europe.
Being a travel geek, I had seen numerous pictures of Hallstatt and had a mental note of visiting this fascinating town someday. This town was on our way to Croatia so we decided to stay there for one night during our European road trip in year 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>God’s Back Garden – the Dolomites, Italy</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_italy_dolomites/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 09:06:52 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_italy_dolomites/</guid>
      <description>God’s Back Garden – the Dolomites, Italy
The Dolomites in the North of Italy boast some of the mightiest granite peaks of Europe. This region is home to a spectacular road that provides both exhilarating and scenic driving.
The breathtaking region around the Dolomites of Italy is one of the most beautiful places on earth. We visited it in October which the fall color was changing that made our road trip more romantic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Square of the Gate of Heavenly Peace - Beijing, China</title>
      <link>/travel/asia_china_beijing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 10:17:52 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/asia_china_beijing/</guid>
      <description>Up there with Times Square in USA, Red Square in Russia, and St. Peter’s Square in Rome, Tiananmen Square in China is among the world’s most famous public spaces. It is the heart of Beijing, China.
                The square is the geographic, political and tourist center of the city, which makes it unavoidable. When I came back from my hometown to Beijing by night train, I made a quick visit at Oct 30, 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation or Duty - China</title>
      <link>/travel/asia_china_shimataigreatwall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 15:37:43 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/asia_china_shimataigreatwall/</guid>
      <description>I gave myself a homework. I need to write a post on my blog after my each trip or adventure. I have came back from China for couple of days but my mind is not calm and I don’t know how to writ down this trip still. It is complicated. This trip mixed with some elements that I hadn’t been experienced yet!
A month ago before my vacation, I borrowed about 20 travel books from the library because I was planning to go to Africa or Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today</title>
      <link>/others/anniversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 15:21:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/anniversary/</guid>
      <description>9/12/2019 Wedding Anniversary Today is mid-autumn festival in China. Today is also my wedding anniversary in US. Today is to remember!
We usually don&amp;rsquo;t celebrate our birthdays. We like to celebrate Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day instead.
Recently, I read a book and it says that treat today is your last day so you won&amp;rsquo;t waste your time! I am to a degree if it is a positive day.
                      6/13/2019 Dating anniversary</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BY THE DEEP BLUE SEA</title>
      <link>/travel/us_ca_la_sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 15:16:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_ca_la_sea/</guid>
      <description>The sea is filled with water, With high and low tides. When we go near it, We feel that we are in paradise! The warmth of the sand touching the feet, The feel of the breeze with a welcoming greet. The sight of the people playing on the shore, Makes my heart roar likes never before! Time flew by as I tried explorer, The beautiful treasures yet the sea bore. Feeling satisfied we flew home, With memories to cherish forever more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall in the Catskills, New York, US</title>
      <link>/travel/us_ny_catskills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 15:09:52 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_ny_catskills/</guid>
      <description>There is no better way to take in the foliage than adventuring outside! This year, Andy and I flew to Albany, NY and then drove about one and half hours to Catskills Mountains in New York State on October 12, 2019. We did the Catskills Mountains Scenic Drive. The roads are winding and surrounded by dense forest with gentle change in elevation. It is a perfect Fall destination. The roads were quiet without too much traffic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Party_Soccer_Team</title>
      <link>/parties/party_soccer_team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 14:40:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/party_soccer_team/</guid>
      <description>This party was finally over and got relief now. Hosting a party for soccer team is stressful than others because they are Andy’s friends. We made food plan together and started to prepare it couple of days earlier in order to make sure the party would be successful.
Bought a box of frozen crab legs from Costco. We decided to serve them a seafood theme dinner.
Appetizers: fried tofu &amp;amp; wonton</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soup_Homemade</title>
      <link>/recipes/soup_homemade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 14:06:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/soup_homemade/</guid>
      <description>I always like soup so I always like to make soup by myself. Because in this way, I will know what ingredients are in my soup. I try to not use high fat items in soup, such as cream, butter etc. My soup is always light with less salt too.
Fish Maw Soup Made this soup with canned sweet corn, fish maw, and egg white.
Fish maw is a good source of collagen, which is vital in healthy skin beauty in all age group of either gender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drink_Homemade</title>
      <link>/recipes/drink_homemade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 13:52:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/drink_homemade/</guid>
      <description>Simple homemade drink without sugar. Can add honey if you have a sweet tooth.
This time I added some turmeric powder. Turmeric, sometimes called Indian saffron or the golden spice.
Positive side effects
While turmeric is a spice, it has also traditionally been used in Chinese medicine to treat inflammatory conditions, skin diseases, wounds, digestive,and liver conditions.
Anti-inflammatory properties
The Arthritis Foundation cites several studies in which turmeric has reduced inflammation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Porridge</title>
      <link>/recipes/porridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 13:48:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/porridge/</guid>
      <description>Congee is a type of rice porridge that is popular in many Asian countries, especially East Asia. When eaten as plain rice congee, it is most often served with side dishes.
Pumpkin porridge
Sweet potato porridge
Taro and purple rice porridge
Green bean, red bean, and black bean porridge. Good for hot and humid summer to get rid of wetness from your body. Pressure cook for 2 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rice_with_sausage</title>
      <link>/recipes/rice_with_sausage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 13:42:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/rice_with_sausage/</guid>
      <description>Rice is important for asian. Just like bread is import for Europen. However, they both have carbs and not really good for diet because they will convert to suger in your body and it may cause diabete problem. So now there are a lot of North American people are skipping carbs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Hot Pot</title>
      <link>/recipes/chinese_hot_pot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 21:54:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/chinese_hot_pot/</guid>
      <description>Hot Pot is a Chinese traditional food. It is usually eat in winter. It is best for a group of friends together. 12/4/2019
                                                        10/6/2019</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Land of Red Rocks - Sedona, AZ</title>
      <link>/travel/us_az_devilsbridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 21:12:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_az_devilsbridge/</guid>
      <description>We were in Sodona, Arizona - the land of red rocks. Flew to Phoenix, AZ airport and then drove 2 hours to Sedona area for a day trip at November 16, 2019. It was a sunny and beautiful day. The temperature was about 70ish degrees without any wind. Arizona is a great escape destination from the cold weather. The song of 500 Miles Away From Home was a perfect song for this scenic road trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geysers – Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_wy_yellowstone_geysers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 10:16:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_wy_yellowstone_geysers/</guid>
      <description>Something from another planet – Geysers, Yellowstone National Park!
 Andy and I landed at Jackson Hole, Wyoming airport at 6pm 8/30/2019. Was planning for this trip for some time now, we were so excited. We have been visited many national parks but Yellowstone is one of my favorites. The park is located mostly in the Northern Wyoming, adjacent to Montana and Idaho states.
Just before landing the view was picturesque.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Independence Holiday, Manhattan NY</title>
      <link>/travel/us_ny_manhattan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 15:30:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_ny_manhattan/</guid>
      <description>“We must be free not because we claim freedom, but because we practice it.” – William Faulkner  This year the independence holiday is Thursday so we took Friday off in order to have a long weekend. I spent 3 hours to find a less crowded flight routes at Tuesday night but seems like not possible. All flights were full with negative numbers. Lot of Americans would travel around the world during this summer that made standby was difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tundra – Rocky Mountain NP, Colorado US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_co_rockymountain_tundra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 10:28:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_co_rockymountain_tundra/</guid>
      <description>Rocky Mountain National Park in Colorado, US encompasses mountains, forests, and alpine tundra. Andy and I visited this park a few times before. This time we just wanted to see tundra.
The word tundra means a land without trees. Tundra is a type of biome where the tree growth is hindered by low temperatures and short growing seasons. There are three types of tundra: Arctic tundra, Alpine tundra, and Antarctica tundra.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Li Dong&#39;s Birthday Party</title>
      <link>/parties/20190421_lidongbday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 21:08:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/20190421_lidongbday/</guid>
      <description>2019-04-21
It is one of Andy’s best friend’s 50th birthday so I hosted a party with a small group for him at my home. I also make a special birthday cake for him and let his wife to write sth on the cake. I also invited another couple who have similar life style like us.
It is also Eastern Weekend so bought fresh flowers for the holiday.                               </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dip into the regions – Highlands, Scotland</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_scotland_highlands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 14:09:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_scotland_highlands/</guid>
      <description>Dip into the regions – Highlands, Scotland
Scotland is one of the most beautiful natural countries around the world. The Scottish Highlands are the home of mountains, glens, and rivers. It is no wonder why they appear as locations in so many movies or TV shows, like Mel Gibson’s self-directed film “Brave Heart”, James Bond’s Skye Fall in “007” movie, “Harry Potter” etc.
There are quite a few ways to get the Highlands, either by train, bus, or car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BAREFOOT ADVENTURE – Edinburgh, Scotland</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_scotland_edinburgh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 14:31:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_scotland_edinburgh/</guid>
      <description>BAREFOOT ADVENTURE – Edinburgh, Scotland
Scotland is an interesting and exciting place to visit. We took a direct flight from Chicago to EDI (Edinburgh International Airport) for my barefoot adventure in July, 2018.
Edinburgh is Scotland’s capital and is not a big city like London and most of attractions are in the medieval old town area, so they are all walking distance. The most interested place is Edinburgh Castle and Royal Miles for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of miles away from home</title>
      <link>/travel/asia_china_shenyang01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 14:51:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/asia_china_shenyang01/</guid>
      <description>Took a week off even though I was very busy at work. My mom planned to go back to China in April. I had to drop her off at our hometown from Windsor, to Chicago, to Beijing, to Shenyang. It was a long trip and would across three countries, Canada, US, and China.
Andy took the Friday off so he flew to Detroit and rented a SUV from Hertz and then drove to Windsor to pick my mom up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CathyPersonalItems</title>
      <link>/others/cathypersonalitems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/cathypersonalitems/</guid>
      <description>Arthritis Patients Respond Very Well to Curcumin Supplements
Arthritis is a common problem in Western countries. There are several different types, most of which involve inflammation in the joints.
Given that curcumin is a potent anti-inflammatory compound, it makes sense that it may help with arthritis. Several studies show this to be true.
In a study in people with rheumatoid arthritis, curcumin was even more effective than an anti-inflammatory drug.Trusted Source</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Temple of the Sea - Monaco</title>
      <link>/europe/monaco/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/monaco/</guid>
      <description>The Principality of Monaco is about 15km (9.3 miles) from the state border with Italy. The city is a resort for tourists and a tax haven for businesses. It is a small country so you can visit it in few hours because the whole state is not larger than 2 square kilometers which is half size of New York&amp;rsquo;s Central Park. We played by ear in this small charm country at Nov 17, 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>