<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NationalParks on Live for Today</title>
    <link>/nationalparks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NationalParks on Live for Today</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 15:01:05 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/nationalparks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden of the Gods, Colorado US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_co_gardenofthegods/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 15:01:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_co_gardenofthegods/</guid>
      <description>Garden of the Gods is on my bucket list for couple of years. My original plan was a weekend trip. However, I made this trip in one day. From Denver airport to the garden was only about one and half hour driving. However, the highway is toll. The round trip cost $35 that was same amount for renting a SUV! That surprised me!
The Colorado landscape looks interesting.
What an adventure!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grand Teton National Park, Wyoming US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_wy_grandteton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 14:50:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_wy_grandteton/</guid>
      <description>Labor Day Weekend Trip
How long haven’t we flied out? Almost two months this summer. Today, we came to the departure lobby in the airport and it looked unfamiliar and we felt we missed it somehow.
This was a busy travel weekend. More and more people took airplanes for traveling. US economy goes very well. We went to economy parking lot G but unfortunately it was full so we had to use our alternative parking lot and then took a cab to the terminal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bison – Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_wy_yellowstone_bison/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 10:22:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_wy_yellowstone_bison/</guid>
      <description>The American bison symbolizes the spirit of the west!
 At the same day seven years ago, Andy and I visited the park and first time saw bison in person. We were so excited but with little nervous. People jumped out of their cars to get closer look at a herd of bison. However, there were rangers with us. So we felt much safer! Picture taken at 9/1/2012
Hayden Valley, Yellowstone NP with its broad expense of grasses, has been a home to bison for thousands of years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geysers – Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_wy_yellowstone_geysers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 10:16:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_wy_yellowstone_geysers/</guid>
      <description>Something from another planet – Geysers, Yellowstone National Park!
 Andy and I landed at Jackson Hole, Wyoming airport at 6pm 8/30/2019. Was planning for this trip for some time now, we were so excited. We have been visited many national parks but Yellowstone is one of my favorites. The park is located mostly in the Northern Wyoming, adjacent to Montana and Idaho states.
Just before landing the view was picturesque.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tundra – Rocky Mountain NP, Colorado US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_co_rockymountain_tundra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 10:28:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_co_rockymountain_tundra/</guid>
      <description>Rocky Mountain National Park in Colorado, US encompasses mountains, forests, and alpine tundra. Andy and I visited this park a few times before. This time we just wanted to see tundra.
The word tundra means a land without trees. Tundra is a type of biome where the tree growth is hindered by low temperatures and short growing seasons. There are three types of tundra: Arctic tundra, Alpine tundra, and Antarctica tundra.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>