<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NationalParks on Live for Today</title>
    <link>/nationalparks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NationalParks on Live for Today</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 18:29:33 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/nationalparks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Rock Canyon National Conservation Area</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_nv_redrockcanyon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 18:29:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_nv_redrockcanyon/</guid>
      <description>We were here to celebrate Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day in year 2020.
Red Rock Canyon National Conservation Area - Absolutely a beautiful sight to behold in the Nevada desert.
Red Rock Canyon National Conservation Area lies in Nevada’s Mojave Desert. It’s known for geological features such as towering red sandstone peaks and the Keystone Thrust Fault, as well as Native American petroglyphs. Panoramic viewing spots dot the 13-mile Scenic Drive. The sheltered Ice Box Canyon has seasonal waterfalls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Land of Extremes - Death Valley National Park</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_nv_deathvalley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_nv_deathvalley/</guid>
      <description>Dec 23, 2019
#Land of Extremes
Death Valley National Park can be summed up in one word: extreme. Because it is the hottest, lowest, and driest place in the United States.
The record high temperature was 134F on July 10, 1913. Death Valley&amp;rsquo;s hottest &amp;ldquo;unoffical&amp;rdquo; temperature was 201F measured on the ground in direct sunlight. By contrast, winter nights can be quiet cool. The colderst temperature recorded at Furnace Creek Ranch was 15F in 1913.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US_CA_PointReyes</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_ca_pointreyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 15:57:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_ca_pointreyes/</guid>
      <description>Point Reyes National Seashore (2018/04/21) 2018-04-22 No Comments
TRAVEL BEYOND THE ORDINARY!
Had scenic drive along California 1 Highway last weekend and continue to explore California 1 Hwy this weekend. This weekend, the weather is very pleasant about 60 to 70 degrees and clear sunny. So I decided to do a day hiking instead of scenic drive.
After doing little homework, I decided Alamere Falls for hiking. Have seen many waterfalls but this is a tidefall which is rare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theodore Roosevelt National Park, North Dakota US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_nd_theodoreroosevelt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 14:25:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_nd_theodoreroosevelt/</guid>
      <description>Theodore Roosevelt National Park, North Dakota US
Cannon Ball 2018-08-31 No Comments
It is Labor Day long weekend. I am trying to be out of town. However, many people are traveling during the long weekend. It makes difficult for standby passengers. I had been search so many destinations but they all seemed full flights.
I am going to try Bismark, ND later today. It is a small express flight that has only 50 seats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US_IN_IndianaDunes</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_in_indianadunes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 12:24:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_in_indianadunes/</guid>
      <description>Indiana Dunes National Lakeshore 2018-08-18 No Comments
Didn’t travel a lot this year since the work kept me crazy busy. Last weekend, I was able to relax in town so our Chinese group went to Indiana Dunes National Lakeshore for a picnic. The weather was about 80F degrees. At the same day, Chicago had Air and Water Show so I thought there weren’t too much people on the beach. As soon as I entered the dunes area, I saw tons of people over there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THE WORLD AT YOUR FEET - Canadian Rocky Mountains</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/canada_rockymountains/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 08:41:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/canada_rockymountains/</guid>
      <description>THE WORLD AT YOUR FEET
Andy and I like adventures. We like to explore new places. We like to try new food. We like new scenic drives. As a world heritage site, Banff National Park offers rugged beauty, unspoiled landscapes and pristine mountain ranges.
Our first visit was at October 15, 2010. At that time, the summer was over and the fall season began. We had to wear our down coats but the scenery was amazing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden of the Gods, Colorado US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_co_gardenofthegods/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 15:01:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_co_gardenofthegods/</guid>
      <description>Garden of the Gods is on my bucket list for couple of years. My original plan was a weekend trip. However, I made this trip in one day. From Denver airport to the garden was only about one and half hour driving. However, the highway is toll. The round trip cost $35 that was same amount for renting a SUV! That surprised me!
The Colorado landscape looks interesting.
What an adventure!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grand Teton National Park, Wyoming US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_wy_grandteton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 14:50:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_wy_grandteton/</guid>
      <description>Labor Day Weekend Trip
How long haven’t we flied out? Almost two months this summer. Today, we came to the departure lobby in the airport and it looked unfamiliar and we felt we missed it somehow.
This was a busy travel weekend. More and more people took airplanes for traveling. US economy goes very well. We went to economy parking lot G but unfortunately it was full so we had to use our alternative parking lot and then took a cab to the terminal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bison – Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_wy_yellowstone_bison/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 10:22:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_wy_yellowstone_bison/</guid>
      <description>The American bison symbolizes the spirit of the west!
 At the same day seven years ago, Andy and I visited the park and first time saw bison in person. We were so excited but with little nervous. People jumped out of their cars to get closer look at a herd of bison. However, there were rangers with us. So we felt much safer! Picture taken at 9/1/2012
Hayden Valley, Yellowstone NP with its broad expense of grasses, has been a home to bison for thousands of years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geysers – Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_wy_yellowstone_geysers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 10:16:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_wy_yellowstone_geysers/</guid>
      <description>Something from another planet – Geysers, Yellowstone National Park!
 Andy and I landed at Jackson Hole, Wyoming airport at 6pm 8/30/2019. Was planning for this trip for some time now, we were so excited. We have been visited many national parks but Yellowstone is one of my favorites. The park is located mostly in the Northern Wyoming, adjacent to Montana and Idaho states.
Just before landing the view was picturesque.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tundra – Rocky Mountain NP, Colorado US</title>
      <link>/nationalparks/us_co_rockymountain_tundra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 10:28:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nationalparks/us_co_rockymountain_tundra/</guid>
      <description>Rocky Mountain National Park in Colorado, US encompasses mountains, forests, and alpine tundra. Andy and I visited this park a few times before. This time we just wanted to see tundra.
The word tundra means a land without trees. Tundra is a type of biome where the tree growth is hindered by low temperatures and short growing seasons. There are three types of tundra: Arctic tundra, Alpine tundra, and Antarctica tundra.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>