<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Travels on Live for Today</title>
    <link>/travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travels on Live for Today</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 09:58:16 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>This Winter, Choose Summer - San Juan, Puerto Rico</title>
      <link>/travel/us_pr_san_juan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 09:58:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_pr_san_juan/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s hard to believe that this exotic is not only close to the United States but also part of it. Puerto Rico is located between the Caribean Sea and the North Atlantic Ocean. You don&amp;rsquo;t need a passport to travel to this American territory.
The island was first ruled by the Spanish until 1898. Present-day Puerto Rico is a major tourist destination, and take pride in their unique combination of heritages: African, Spanish, and North American.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Winter, Choose Summer - Honeymoon Island, FL</title>
      <link>/travel/us_fl_tampa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_fl_tampa/</guid>
      <description>When Chicago had winterstorms in January, I escaped to Tampa, FL for the sunny and warm weather. Tampa is a city on Tampa Bay, along Florida’s Gulf Coast. There are so many beaches in Clearwater area and my mood was to be a sun-seeker on a white sand beach.
              Honeymoon Island This island formally known as Hog Island, Honeymoon Island acquired its current name when a New Yorker purchased the island in 1939 and built bungalows for honeymooners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Road Trip from Los Angeles to San Deigo</title>
      <link>/travel/us_ca_sandiego/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 08:49:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_ca_sandiego/</guid>
      <description>A Road Trip from Los Angeles to San Deigo
2018-05-09 1 Comment
Driving along the coast and stunning views – A road trip from Los Angeles to San Diego, CA!
It was Friday afternoon. I was checking the flight to Seattle. Flight status looked good for standbys but I wasn’t sure if it would be a good time to visit Mt Rainier National Park. The park is at high elevation so the temperature will be colder than sea level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US_NM_SantaFe</title>
      <link>/travel/us_nm_santafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 16:03:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_nm_santafe/</guid>
      <description>Protected: Iceland &amp;gt;&amp;gt; New Mexico 2018-05-20 No Comments
5/25/2018 Friday ORD – ABQ
5/26/2018 Saturday Pistachio Tour in NM White Sands National Monument
5/27/2018 Sunday Taos Peublo Village
5/28/2018 Monday Santa Fe, NM Kash-Katuwe Tent Rocks National Monument
5/29/2018 Tuesday ABQ – LAX LAX – ORD
5/29/2018 Tuesday Flying Home
Time to flying home after my adventure. Since I skipped visiting the Carlsbad Caverns National Park, I decided to go home one day earlier as my planned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Hours in Memphis, TN</title>
      <link>/travel/us_tn_memphis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 15:09:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_tn_memphis/</guid>
      <description>Protected: 20 Hours in Memphis, TN 2018-06-17 1 Comment
Group of four to Memphis, Tennessee. This sounds unusual to me. The flight to MEM was wide open so Dan and his girlfriend also want to visit Memphis. All of us had never been to Memphis yet. So we decided to explore the city together.
Before we made the decision to go together, I sent them my itinerary to checkif they can follow my schedule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US_WashingtonDC</title>
      <link>/travel/us_washingtondc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 14:10:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_washingtondc/</guid>
      <description>RUNNING WHILE TRAVELING – DC 2018-09-20 1 Comment
RUN WHILE TRAVELING
From now on, I will bring my running shoes with me when I travel. Running is a great workout. It is not only for body but for mind. So I ran when I traveled to DC this time and feeling was great.
Bought one-way ticket to Washington DC today. Didn’t get time to do travel research until last night. DC has many museums and history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US_NV_ValleyOfFireStatePark</title>
      <link>/travel/us_nv_valleyoffirestatepark/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 10:21:31 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_nv_valleyoffirestatepark/</guid>
      <description>Valley of Fire State Park is a public recreation and nature preservation area covering nearly 46,000 acres located 16 miles south of Overton, Nevada. The state park derives its name from red sandstone formations, the Aztec Sandstone, which formed from shifting sand dunes 150 million years ago.
Address: 29450 Valley of Fire Hwy, Overton, NV 89040
Valley of Fire State Park
Valley of Fire is located in the Mojave Desert approximately 58 miles Northeast of the Las Vegas Strip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US_FL_Miami</title>
      <link>/travel/us_fl_miami/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:10:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_fl_miami/</guid>
      <description>2018-12-27 No Comments
A day trip to Miami, FL. Left home at 4am in the morning and back home at 10pm in the evening. Was at Miami about 4 hours but it was a surprised and unplanned trip! The flight was already full. I didn’t think I could have a chance! The departure time was at 7:10am and we got assigned seats at 7am. It was really a surprise. The sky was still dark at 7am.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US_CA_BigSur</title>
      <link>/travel/us_ca_bigsur/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:05:39 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_ca_bigsur/</guid>
      <description>Protected: Big Sur, CA 2018-12-27 No Comments
Big Sur is a rugged stretch of California’s central coast between Carmel and San Simeon. Bordered to the east by the Santa Lucia Mountains and the west by the Pacific Ocean, it’s traversed by narrow, 2-lane State Route 1, known for winding turns, seaside cliffs and views of the often-misty coastline. The sparsely populated region has numerous state parks for hiking, camping and beachcombing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US_TX_SanAntonio</title>
      <link>/travel/us_tx_sanantonio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 13:19:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_tx_sanantonio/</guid>
      <description>San Antonio, TX 2019-02-13 No Comments
San Antonio Missions National Historical Park
Visitor Center – Visitor Center at Mission San José
Open seven days a week from 9 am – 5 pm
6701 San Jose Drive, San Antonio, TX 78214
Mission Addresses
Mission Concepción 807 Mission Road, San Antonio, Texas 78210
Mission San José 6701 San Jose Drive, San Antonio, TX 78214
Mission San Juan 9101 Graf Road, San Antonio, Texas 78214</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running while Traveling – Dallas, Texas</title>
      <link>/travel/us_tx_dallas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 21:33:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_tx_dallas/</guid>
      <description>A short trip to Dallas, TX. This was my 2nd time to land at DFW airport. A couple of years ago, I was here for a Microsoft Ignite Training where was located in Irving, TX. I did some travel research about Dallas but it seems a little boring city for me because I was looking for some outdoor activities. However, Dallas is a very flat area without mountains. I wasn’t able to find things that I really wanted to explore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>La La Trip</title>
      <link>/travel/us_ca_antelopevalley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 15:12:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_ca_antelopevalley/</guid>
      <description>The movie of La La Land explores the joy and pain of pursuing their dreams in Los Angeles, CA. I watched this movie last year. It was a great story even though they couldn’t be together at the end but the girl fulfilled her dream in Hollywood.
I haven’t visited La La Land for couple of years so we flew to LAX at midnight of 4/12/2019. It was poppy flower season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O Canada – Visiting Windsor, Ontario</title>
      <link>/travel/canada_on_windsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 10:26:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/canada_on_windsor/</guid>
      <description>O Canada! Our home and native land!
True patriot love in all of us command.
 Canada was the first foreign country where I went abroad. I dealt with a new language, new way of thinking, new culture, which opened my eyes and changed my perspective of life completely.
Windsor, Ontario Canada is the place actually changed me. I consider it as my second hometown because not only I got my CS degree but my mom is living there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Square of the Gate of Heavenly Peace - Beijing, China</title>
      <link>/travel/asia_china_beijing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 10:17:52 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/asia_china_beijing/</guid>
      <description>Up there with Times Square in USA, Red Square in Russia, and St. Peter’s Square in Rome, Tiananmen Square in China is among the world’s most famous public spaces. It is the heart of Beijing, China.
                The square is the geographic, political and tourist center of the city, which makes it unavoidable. When I came back from my hometown to Beijing by night train, I made a quick visit at Oct 30, 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation or Duty - China</title>
      <link>/travel/asia_china_shimataigreatwall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 15:37:43 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/asia_china_shimataigreatwall/</guid>
      <description>I gave myself a homework. I need to write a post on my blog after my each trip or adventure. I have came back from China for couple of days but my mind is not calm and I don’t know how to writ down this trip still. It is complicated. This trip mixed with some elements that I hadn’t been experienced yet!
A month ago before my vacation, I borrowed about 20 travel books from the library because I was planning to go to Africa or Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BY THE DEEP BLUE SEA</title>
      <link>/travel/us_ca_la_sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 15:16:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_ca_la_sea/</guid>
      <description>The sea is filled with water, With high and low tides. When we go near it, We feel that we are in paradise! The warmth of the sand touching the feet, The feel of the breeze with a welcoming greet. The sight of the people playing on the shore, Makes my heart roar likes never before! Time flew by as I tried explorer, The beautiful treasures yet the sea bore. Feeling satisfied we flew home, With memories to cherish forever more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall in the Catskills, New York, US</title>
      <link>/travel/us_ny_catskills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 15:09:52 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_ny_catskills/</guid>
      <description>There is no better way to take in the foliage than adventuring outside! This year, Andy and I flew to Albany, NY and then drove about one and half hours to Catskills Mountains in New York State on October 12, 2019. We did the Catskills Mountains Scenic Drive. The roads are winding and surrounded by dense forest with gentle change in elevation. It is a perfect Fall destination. The roads were quiet without too much traffic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Land of Red Rocks - Sedona, AZ</title>
      <link>/travel/us_az_devilsbridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 21:12:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_az_devilsbridge/</guid>
      <description>We were in Sodona, Arizona - the land of red rocks. Flew to Phoenix, AZ airport and then drove 2 hours to Sedona area for a day trip at November 16, 2019. It was a sunny and beautiful day. The temperature was about 70ish degrees without any wind. Arizona is a great escape destination from the cold weather. The song of 500 Miles Away From Home was a perfect song for this scenic road trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Independence Holiday, Manhattan NY</title>
      <link>/travel/us_ny_manhattan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 15:30:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/us_ny_manhattan/</guid>
      <description>“We must be free not because we claim freedom, but because we practice it.” – William Faulkner  This year the independence holiday is Thursday so we took Friday off in order to have a long weekend. I spent 3 hours to find a less crowded flight routes at Tuesday night but seems like not possible. All flights were full with negative numbers. Lot of Americans would travel around the world during this summer that made standby was difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of miles away from home</title>
      <link>/travel/asia_china_shenyang01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 14:51:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/asia_china_shenyang01/</guid>
      <description>Took a week off even though I was very busy at work. My mom planned to go back to China in April. I had to drop her off at our hometown from Windsor, to Chicago, to Beijing, to Shenyang. It was a long trip and would across three countries, Canada, US, and China.
Andy took the Friday off so he flew to Detroit and rented a SUV from Hertz and then drove to Windsor to pick my mom up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An ancient city where every stone has a story to tell - Jerusalem, Israel</title>
      <link>/travel/israel_jerusalem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travel/israel_jerusalem/</guid>
      <description>Life is about making memories. I had an unforgettable solo trip to Jerusalem, Israel a couple of years ago. As soon as I stood at the Jaffa Gate of this ancient walled city, I was speechless. More than beautiful, Jerusalem is a spiritual center, holy to the three religions. That three religions have assigned so much importance to a solitary city makes Jerusalem one of the most fascinating places I have ever visited.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>