<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Europes on Live for Today</title>
    <link>/europe/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Europes on Live for Today</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 10:08:04 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/europe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow in the footsteps of “Game of Thrones” - Dubrovnik, Croatia</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_croatia_dubrovnik/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 10:08:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_croatia_dubrovnik/</guid>
      <description>It’s not easy being drunk all the time. If it were easy, everyone would do it. – Tyrion Lannister
 Game of Thrones is likely one of the most talked about TV shows of the decade and Dubrovnik, Croatia has been a renowned Game of Thrones filming location. After all Dubrovnik is King’s Landing, the capital of the Seven Kingdoms! Dubrovnik’s architecture, City Walls, its open and narrow streets made of big stone blocks helped Dubrovnik to change personality quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A “real life” Postcard – Hallstatt, Austria</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_austria_hallstatt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 09:32:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_austria_hallstatt/</guid>
      <description>Hallstatt is an umber-picturesque town in Austria. Surrounded by the massive Dachstein mountains, this town is a visual treat to the sore eyes. It features on the list of most romantic towns in Europe.
Being a travel geek, I had seen numerous pictures of Hallstatt and had a mental note of visiting this fascinating town someday. This town was on our way to Croatia so we decided to stay there for one night during our European road trip in year 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>God’s Back Garden – the Dolomites, Italy</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_italy_dolomites/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 09:06:52 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_italy_dolomites/</guid>
      <description>God’s Back Garden – the Dolomites, Italy
The Dolomites in the North of Italy boast some of the mightiest granite peaks of Europe. This region is home to a spectacular road that provides both exhilarating and scenic driving.
The breathtaking region around the Dolomites of Italy is one of the most beautiful places on earth. We visited it in October which the fall color was changing that made our road trip more romantic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dip into the regions – Highlands, Scotland</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_scotland_highlands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 14:09:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_scotland_highlands/</guid>
      <description>Dip into the regions – Highlands, Scotland
Scotland is one of the most beautiful natural countries around the world. The Scottish Highlands are the home of mountains, glens, and rivers. It is no wonder why they appear as locations in so many movies or TV shows, like Mel Gibson’s self-directed film “Brave Heart”, James Bond’s Skye Fall in “007” movie, “Harry Potter” etc.
There are quite a few ways to get the Highlands, either by train, bus, or car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BAREFOOT ADVENTURE – Edinburgh, Scotland</title>
      <link>/europe/eu_scotland_edinburgh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 14:31:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/eu_scotland_edinburgh/</guid>
      <description>BAREFOOT ADVENTURE – Edinburgh, Scotland
Scotland is an interesting and exciting place to visit. We took a direct flight from Chicago to EDI (Edinburgh International Airport) for my barefoot adventure in July, 2018.
Edinburgh is Scotland’s capital and is not a big city like London and most of attractions are in the medieval old town area, so they are all walking distance. The most interested place is Edinburgh Castle and Royal Miles for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Temple of the Sea - Monaco</title>
      <link>/europe/monaco/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/europe/monaco/</guid>
      <description>The Principality of Monaco is about 15km (9.3 miles) from the state border with Italy. The city is a resort for tourists and a tax haven for businesses. It is a small country so you can visit it in few hours because the whole state is not larger than 2 square kilometers which is half size of New York&amp;rsquo;s Central Park. We played by ear in this small charm country at Nov 17, 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>