<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Parties on Live for Today</title>
    <link>/parties/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Parties on Live for Today</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 10:17:46 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/parties/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>NewYearEve_2017</title>
      <link>/parties/newyeareve_2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 10:17:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/newyeareve_2017/</guid>
      <description>Happy Christmas Eve!! I can’t believe today is the last post in the advent calendar series. I’ve had SO much fun bringing you guys a new post every day, and today, we’re finishing with a nice, celebratory festive cocktail!
Every year, I look forward to the festive period so much, then it turns up and is crazier and busier than the year and Christmas day arrives before we know it and somehow I wish I’d taken it a bit slower and spent more time just being in this season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NewYearEve_2016</title>
      <link>/parties/newyeareve_2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 10:06:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/newyeareve_2016/</guid>
      <description>New Year Eve Party – 2016/12/31 2018-12-05 No Comments
7 Lucky Foods to Eat on New Year&#39;s Day Black-Eyed Peas, Greens, and Cornbread. Luck factor: Even folks who aren&#39;t from the Southern United States go all in on eating black-eyed peas and leafy greens for good luck on New Year&#39;s Day. ... Pork. Luck factor: Pork for progress! ... Grapes. ... Pomegranates. ... Fish. ... Noodles and Rice. ... Cakes.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NewYearEve_2013</title>
      <link>/parties/newyeareve_2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:59:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/newyeareve_2013/</guid>
      <description>New Year Eve Party – 2013/12/31 2018-12-05 No Comments
You can&amp;rsquo;t just pop a bottle and call it a night. If you&amp;rsquo;re hosting a New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve party or pregame this year, you need to go all out. Whether you want to go bold, boho, or keep it elegant, we&amp;rsquo;ve got plenty of ideas on this list to make sure yours is a party for the books. Ahead, fifteen New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve party ideas that promise 2020 will begin on a strong note.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NewYearEve_2018</title>
      <link>/parties/newyeareve_2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:55:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/newyeareve_2018/</guid>
      <description>New Year Eve Party – 2018/12/31 2018-12-16 No Comments Fried Wonton &amp;amp; Tofu Salted Duck
To absolutely no one’s surprise, there is A LOT to see and do this New Year’s Eve in Chicago. And while we’ve been toiling away at our desks, we’ve also been daydreaming about all the events, parties, and down-right blowouts we could be going to on the 31st.
The good news? Since we’ve spent so much time thinking about it, we’ve actually been able to compile a pretty solid list of the best celebrations around the city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CookingWithCathy_Dumpling</title>
      <link>/parties/cookingwithcathy_dumpling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 10:55:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/cookingwithcathy_dumpling/</guid>
      <description>Rainbow Dumpling
Protected: Rainbow Dumpling 2019-03-29
I grouped few people together who have same interest about cooking. Rainbow dumpling is our first episode of Cooking with Cathy! They brought dumpling fillings and I prepared doughs. We made wraps and dumplings together. That was fun time with friends.
I got the idea from Pinterest app. We are not only making food but for fun!
4 of us made dumplings Spinach, beets, water Pan fried pot stickers Steamed dumplings We all enjoyed our dumplings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CookingWithCathy_Fondue</title>
      <link>/parties/cookingwithcathy_fondue/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 10:38:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/cookingwithcathy_fondue/</guid>
      <description>2019-04-22
Still can’t get together with other friends yet since we all are busy here and there. However our next party will be fondue party. I did some research about food.
4/28/2019 seems another winterstorm day. I was planning out of town but the weather forecast freaked me out. It is better to stay at home to worry free about flights. So I contacted my friends right after work at Friday to gather people together for the Fondue Party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CookingWithCathy_Noodle</title>
      <link>/parties/cookingwithcathy_noodle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 10:32:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/cookingwithcathy_noodle/</guid>
      <description>Cooking with Cathy – episode 3.
Today is also the last day for Game of Thrones. We are all fan of it so I got together to cook first and then watch the finale together at my basement.
The ending of Game of Thrones made people upset. However, I think that is what it is. No matter what kind of ending is, people will always not satisfied. For me, I think, the story is not ending yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cooking with Cathy - Kebab</title>
      <link>/parties/cookingwithcathy_kebab/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 08:30:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/cookingwithcathy_kebab/</guid>
      <description>Cooking with Cathy – episode 4.
Hosted this episode with friends before the summer end. It was a pleasant Saturday afternoon, we made charcoal grilled kebab together.
Actually, I did shopping at Friday and prepared food since Friday evening. I just let them to put chunked lamb on skewers. If I waited them to make food from scratch, it would take hours to finish.
Cooking with Cathy is just for fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Party_Soccer_Team</title>
      <link>/parties/party_soccer_team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 14:40:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/party_soccer_team/</guid>
      <description>This party was finally over and got relief now. Hosting a party for soccer team is stressful than others because they are Andy’s friends. We made food plan together and started to prepare it couple of days earlier in order to make sure the party would be successful.
Bought a box of frozen crab legs from Costco. We decided to serve them a seafood theme dinner.
Appetizers: fried tofu &amp;amp; wonton</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gourmet Chinese Food</title>
      <link>/parties/chunhuangcooking_20190810/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/chunhuangcooking_20190810/</guid>
      <description>Gourmet Chinese Food
One of my friends is really good at cooking Chinese food. It is not only delicious but beautiful presentation! They are much better than restaurant food.
She spent lot of time to prepare them from scratch. We always eat more than we could.
This is seafood soup which I like it very much.
The crispy basil is so impressive.
Japanese rice wine from Costco. This tea set cost RMB 5000 because they made with pure gold and silver!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Li Dong&#39;s Birthday Party</title>
      <link>/parties/20190421_lidongbday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 21:08:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/20190421_lidongbday/</guid>
      <description>2019-04-21
It is one of Andy’s best friend’s 50th birthday so I hosted a party with a small group for him at my home. I also make a special birthday cake for him and let his wife to write sth on the cake. I also invited another couple who have similar life style like us.
It is also Eastern Weekend so bought fresh flowers for the holiday.                               </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Party_Chinese_Crab</title>
      <link>/parties/party_chinese_crab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parties/party_chinese_crab/</guid>
      <description>Crab Party 2018-10-21 No Comments
I am terrified of nightclubs. I hate loud bars. And I get lost at concerts. This makes Friday and Saturday nights as a non-80 something difficult.
As soon as it was socially age appropriate, I began to shift people from raves and bar crawls into game nights and dinner parties.
My first dinner party was a quasi-disaster. There were a ton of appetizers and dessert, but not enough real food.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>