<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Restaurants on Live for Today</title>
    <link>/restaurant/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Restaurants on Live for Today</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 08:59:16 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/restaurant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Spice &amp; Rice Kitchen, San Diego CA</title>
      <link>/restaurant/spicericethaikitchen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 08:59:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/spicericethaikitchen/</guid>
      <description>Spice &amp;amp; Rice Kitchen Address: 7734 Girard Ave C, La Jolla, CA 92037
Unpretentious destination for exotic Thai dishes &amp;amp; lunch combos inside or on the fountainside patio.
We are a Thai restaurant that caters to local La Jolla and San Diego residents area. Our food is freshly made and is vegetarian friendly with no MSG added. Takes Reservations, Walk-Ins Welcome, Good For Groups, Good For Kids, Take Out, Delivery, Catering, Waiter Service and Outdoor Seating</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morton_Steakhouse</title>
      <link>/restaurant/morton_steakhouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 14:57:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/morton_steakhouse/</guid>
      <description>Morton’s The Steakhouse
Morton&amp;rsquo;s The Steakhouse is a chain of steak restaurants with locations in the United States and franchised abroad, founded in Chicago in 1978. It is a wholly owned subsidiary of Landry&amp;rsquo;s, Inc.
Morton&amp;rsquo;s The Steakhouse at Wacker Place is located at the epicenter of some of Downtown Chicago&amp;rsquo;s most celebrated attractions and downtown hotels. Walking distance from the Magnificent Mile, Millennium Park and the Chicago Theatre District, this steakhouse offers a superb dining location for a business power lunch, after work drinks and small plate $5 Bar Bites, an exceptional dinner or even over 4,000 square feet of private dining space in six private dining rooms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sam &amp; Harry’s Steakhouse</title>
      <link>/restaurant/sam_harry_steakhouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 14:52:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/sam_harry_steakhouse/</guid>
      <description>Sam &amp;amp; Harry’s Steakhouse Sam_Harry_Steakhouse 2019-01-27
Upscale, contemporary steakhouse serving surf &amp;lsquo;n&amp;rsquo; turf classics in the Renaissance Schaumburg Hotel. Address: 1551 Thoreau Dr N, Schaumburg, IL 60173
Sam &amp;amp; Harry&amp;rsquo;s is about savoring the high life. Enjoy innovative cuisine, prime steaks, and fine seafood in an upscale, inviting atmosphere. Our inspired contemporary American menu celebrates thoughtful preparations of the freshest ingredients from local farms, and our Award-Winning wine program includes 250 wines by the bottle and over 50 by the glass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lao Sze Chuan</title>
      <link>/restaurant/lao_sze_chuan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 10:49:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/lao_sze_chuan/</guid>
      <description>Lao Sze Chuan Address: 520 N Michigan Ave, Chicago IL
Spicy and salty dishes for me so I am not crazy about this place even though it is a famous restaurant. Spicy and salty dishes for me so I am not crazy about this place even though it is a famous restaurant. Spicy and salty dishes for me so I am not crazy about this place even though it is a famous restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet Fresh Dessert Restaurnat</title>
      <link>/restaurant/meetfresh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 15:32:44 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/meetfresh/</guid>
      <description>Meet Fresh Dessert Restaurnat 鮮芋仙
Meet Fresh is a Taiwanese dessert restaurant chain, with locations in Asia, Australia, New Zealand, Canada and the United States. Corporate headquarters are in New Taipei City. Founded in 2007, the chain specializes in fresh Taiwanese desserts, including soft taro balls and herbed jelly.
Bottom is shaved ice. Authentic Taiwanese exquisite desserts
Sister and Brother Fu grew up in a family which has been farming for generations in the Feng Yuan District of Taichung, Taiwan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Din Tai Fung</title>
      <link>/restaurant/din_tai_fung/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 15:15:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/din_tai_fung/</guid>
      <description>Din Tai Feng Restaurant 鼎泰豐
Din Tai Fung is a Taiwanese restaurant franchise, specialising in Huaiyang cuisine. Outside Taiwan, Din Tai Fung also has branches in Australia, China, Hong Kong, Indonesia, Japan, Macau, Malaysia, Philippines, Singapore, South Korea, United States, Thailand, UK and the UAE. It is a world-renowned Taiwanese restaurant that specializes in soup dumplings and noodles.
Xiao Long Bao is their signature food.
              </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBQ_Garden</title>
      <link>/restaurant/bbq_garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/restaurant/bbq_garden/</guid>
      <description>BBQ Garden
My friend invited us to her birthday at BBQ Garden this Saturday 6/22/2019. Met few new friends. Also table grilled BBQ was delicious.
It is buffet style BBQ. You can order as much as you can eat. There are many meat options but my favorite is still beef short ribs.
They also include sushi and Korean style side dishes. I like this restaurant. I would go back!
I made the cake for her and everyone likes my cake.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>