<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Others on Live for Today</title>
    <link>/others/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Others on Live for Today</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 11:18:50 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/others/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CathySummary</title>
      <link>/others/cathysummary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 11:18:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/cathysummary/</guid>
      <description>It is almost end of the year again. Time flies and I need to pause here and recall what have I done during year 2019.
Year 2019
 Starting reading books
 This is becoming a new hobby to me. I met a new friend who introduced me to join a reading club on WeChat. We were supposed to read a book each month. We just need to read 25 mins a day but we need to write down a summary after reading each day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flying Home</title>
      <link>/others/flyinghome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 08:46:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/flyinghome/</guid>
      <description>10/23/2019
We got a room available for my mom in this senior house so we decided to go back to my hometown together.
The trip was smooth even though it was a long international trip from US to Canada to US to China. We had 4 connections. Andy and I didn’t sleep too much during this trip because the schedule was very tight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today</title>
      <link>/others/anniversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 15:21:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/anniversary/</guid>
      <description>Today is mid-autumn festival in China. Today is also my wedding anniversary in US. Today is to remember!
We usually don&amp;rsquo;t celebrate our birthdays. We like to celebrate Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day instead.
Recently, I read a book and it says that treat today is your last day so you won&amp;rsquo;t waste your time! I am to a degree if it is a positive day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>