<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Others on Live for Today</title>
    <link>/others/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Others on Live for Today</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 14:31:14 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/others/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Starry Starry Night</title>
      <link>/others/song_starrynight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 14:31:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/song_starrynight/</guid>
      <description>Starry, starry night
Paint your palette blue and grey
Look out on a summer’s day
With eyes that know the darkness in my soul
Shadows on the hills
Sketch the trees and the daffodils
Catch the breeze and the winter chills
In colors on the snowy linen land
 Vincent Van Gogh – one of the world’s foremost artists. I like few of his colorful and dynamic paints, Starry Starry Night and Sunflowers!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Book</title>
      <link>/others/movie_greenbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 14:24:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/movie_greenbook/</guid>
      <description>Green Book, this is the first movie that I watched since this year. The film is inspired by the true story of a tour of the Deep South by Jamaican-American classical &amp;amp; jazz pianist and Italian-American bounder who served as a driver &amp;amp; bodyguard.
The film won the Oscar Academy Award for Best Picture, as well as Best Original Screenplay and Best Supporting Actor and was also nominated for Best Actor and Best Film Editing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones</title>
      <link>/others/tvshow_gameofthrones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 14:19:42 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/tvshow_gameofthrones/</guid>
      <description>I had been watching GOT all seasons 2 times. However, I still like it very much and now I start watching GOT from season 1 again. This time, I feel I could understand it better than last time. 7 Kingdoms, which one do I like most? The Queen, the dragon mother, Jon Snow? I have to think about it!
4/14/2019
Tonight will have Game of Thrones season 8. This will be the last season of Game of Thrones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadership</title>
      <link>/others/leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 13:46:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/leadership/</guid>
      <description>Year 2018
Year 2017
From around the globe, more than 2,000 leaders came together to celebrate our people, our potential and our passion. Luckily, I had the opportunity to attend this 3-day event. We deepened our understanding of the ecompany’s most important priorities, and continued to build momentum and values and leadership model.
10 ways to have a better conversation
 No multi-task (Put away your phone / Focus on conversation) No lecture participate (Don’t change sb’s mind / Better listener / Everyone you’ll meet, you will learn!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sun-Worshipping Plants</title>
      <link>/others/sunworshippingplants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 13:41:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/sunworshippingplants/</guid>
      <description>Barrington Hills Farm Address: 2790 Spring Creek Road, Barrington Hills, IL 60010
My friend posts some sunflower pictures on WeChat Moments. So I was curious where she went for taking those beautiful sunflower pictures. Surprisingly, it is in Barrington Hills, IL. I was so excited and invited my other friends to go together for photo shooting.
Usually, the best time for taking picture is either morning or sunset time. We went over there at Sunday late afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>365 Miles</title>
      <link>/others/365miles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 12:54:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/365miles/</guid>
      <description>7/12/2019
I wrote down what I ate for couple of weeks and I think they are pretty healthy food with low carb. However I still have fat belly. I am not sure what is wrong with my diet or exercise until yesterday!
In a new WeChat Tomato Group that are people who had reading a book for 14 days, I found out the root cause.
有氧无氧是指糖在运动中是无氧代谢还是有氧代谢。有氧代谢一个葡萄糖能产生38个ATP供细胞使用，过程比较慢。走路就是有氧运动。剧烈运动的时候是无氧代谢，快速产生ATP, 副产品就是乳酸
So it means I should do intense exercise, like short distance and full speed running instead of walking for 30 mins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Club</title>
      <link>/others/bookreading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 11:59:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/bookreading/</guid>
      <description>I usually don&amp;rsquo;t read a book until this year. Now reading becomes a new hobby for me.
 The goal of higher income is not just bigger piles of money. The goal of longer lives is not jsut extra time. The ultimate goal is to have the freedom to do what we want.
from book of Factufulness
 Reading Activity  The Thorn Birds Novel (online) Day Trading for Dummies, 4th Edition (Safari Bookshelf) Managing the Unmanageable Rules, Tools, and Insights for Managing Software Poeple and Teams Never Split the Difference Becoming by Michelle Obama Meditation &amp;amp; Mindfulness                Read Books in Year 2019  Never Split the Difference (2019&amp;frasl;08)  This book was recommanded by WeChat Reading Club and they also shared the book URL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CathySummary</title>
      <link>/others/cathysummary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 11:18:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/cathysummary/</guid>
      <description>Year 2020 Planns
 A new song / month Reading Finance investment Travel journey Travel AWS Cert  It is almost end of the year again. Time flies and I need to pause here and recall what have I done during year 2019.
Year 2019
 Starting reading books
 This is becoming a new hobby to me. I met a new friend who introduced me to join a reading club on WeChat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flying Home</title>
      <link>/others/flyinghome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 08:46:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/flyinghome/</guid>
      <description>10/23/2019
We got a room available for my mom in this senior house so we decided to go back to my hometown together.
The trip was smooth even though it was a long international trip from US to Canada to US to China. We had 4 connections. Andy and I didn’t sleep too much during this trip because the schedule was very tight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today</title>
      <link>/others/anniversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 15:21:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/anniversary/</guid>
      <description>9/12/2019 Wedding Anniversary Today is mid-autumn festival in China. Today is also my wedding anniversary in US. Today is to remember!
We usually don&amp;rsquo;t celebrate our birthdays. We like to celebrate Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day instead.
Recently, I read a book and it says that treat today is your last day so you won&amp;rsquo;t waste your time! I am to a degree if it is a positive day.
                      6/13/2019 Dating anniversary</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CathyPersonalItems</title>
      <link>/others/cathypersonalitems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/cathypersonalitems/</guid>
      <description>Arthritis Patients Respond Very Well to Curcumin Supplements
Arthritis is a common problem in Western countries. There are several different types, most of which involve inflammation in the joints.
Given that curcumin is a potent anti-inflammatory compound, it makes sense that it may help with arthritis. Several studies show this to be true.
In a study in people with rheumatoid arthritis, curcumin was even more effective than an anti-inflammatory drug.Trusted Source</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>